were
estábamos
Okay we were
Okay estábamos
[Music]
[Música]
here we go
here we
the family here perform it for you if
go the family here perform it for you if
you know the words you can join In To put
you know the words you can join In To
your hands Together if you W Clap as
put your hands Together if you W Clap as
we take you through this monkey
we take you through this monkey
rap Donkey
rap Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong H He's the leader of
Kong Donkey Kong H He's the leader of
the bunch you know him well He's Finally
the bunch you know him well He's Finally
back to Kick some his Coconut
back to Kick some his Coconut
gum and sps If he
gum and sps If he
shoots G
shoots G
he bigger faster and stronger to First
he bigger faster and stronger to First
member
member
of believed
of
Kong Donkey Kong
Kong Donkey Kong
iskey
iskey
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Donkey
Donkey
Kong Donkey
Kong Donkey
Kong this got so Listen up to ink
Kong this got so Listen up
size to suit her She's quick and n
toink size to suit her She's quick and n
When She needs to be She can float
When She needs to be She can float
through the air and Climb up Tree you
through the air and Climb up Tree you
choose her You're not choosing wrong with
choose her You're not choose wrong with
a skip and a H She's One
a skip and a H She's One
cool Donkey
cool Donkey
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music] Kong
[Música]
Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
here Donkey Kong
here Donkey
Donkey Kong is here has no Style he has no
Kong Donkey Kong is here has no Style he
Grace this has a funny Face he can hand
Grace this has a funny Face he can
when he needs to and stretch his
hand when he needs to and stretch his
Arms  out Just for you inflate yourself
Arms out Just for you inflate himself
just like  a balloon this Crazy Just digs
just like a balloon this Crazy Just digs
tuney
tuney
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Kong Donkey Kong is here
Donkey
Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
[Music] kke Kong
[Música]
He's Back Again and about time
kke Kong He's Back Again and about time
to and this Time He's in the moon he can fly
to and this Time He's in the moon he can
real with Jet with his pistols out
fly real with Jet with his pistols out
He's One tough he'll Make You Smile when
He's One tough he'll Make You Smile when
he Play his butlin beware he after you
he Play his butlin beware he after you
Donkey
Donkey
[Music]
[Música]
Kong Donkey Kong is
Kong Donkey Kong is
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
here Donkey
here Donkey
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally He's here
Kong Donkey Kong is Finally He's here
for you  It's The Last member of the dk
for you It's The Last member of the dk
Crew this K so strong it isn't funny ain
Crew this K so strong it isn't funny ain
Cry out for mmy pick up a b relative
Cry out for mmy pick up a b relative
ease makes crushing Rocks seem such a
ease makes crushing Rocks seem such a
breeze he May move Slow he can't jump
breeze he May move Slow he can't jump
but this One Hell Of A Come on cranky
but this One Hell Of A Come on cranky
take it to the fridge
take it to the fridge
[Music]
[Música]
walut peut pineapp smell graes Mel
walut peut pineapp smell graes Mel
oranges and Coconut shell oh yeah
oranges and Coconut shell oh yeah
walnuts peut pineapple
walnuts peut pineapple
smells melons oranges and Coconut shells
smells melons oranges and Coconut shells
oh yeah walnuts  peanuts pineapple
oh yeah walnuts peanuts pineapple
smells melons oranges and coconut shell
smells melons oranges and Coconut shell
oh yeah walut peut  pell
oh yeah walut peut pell
[Music]
[Música]
Hey guys can you hear me
Hola guapos me escucháis
okay How are you guys
Bien Qué tal
Let's see the reality is that it wasn't going to be
estáis a ver la realidad es que no iba a
live today here eh
ser directo hoy aquí eh
Franco this one went cool all of a sudden no
Franco esta se volvió Guay de golpe no
but let's see is it plex's fault a little let's
pero a ver es culpa de plex un poco a
see I'm going to put it out but not so
ver voy a poner a luz pero no
much you famos if you don't do live today let's
tanto te famos si no haces directo hoy a
see wlo It's that things are very
ver wlo Es que la cosa hoy está muy
calm today and I'm look I'll explain
calmadita y estoy mira os explico
Wait they're talking to me on
Espérate que me están hablando por
WhatsApp something that I'm going to read
whatspp una cosa que voy a leer
e It's that I have a recorded news I have a recorded newscast of
e Es que tengo un noti grabado tengo un
course I have a recorded newscast
claro tengo un noticiero
[Music] I have
[Música]
a recorded newscast
grabado tengo un noticiero grabado
because I recorded it before going to the gym
porque lo grabé antes de irme a gimnasio
but the editor is Ah busy Today No today
pero está el editor Ah liado Hoy No hoy
Aiden that Aiden is busy with something today
aiden que está liado aiden con algo hoy
and and we don't have the thumbnail yet
y y no tenemos la miniatura todavía
so it's like several contents are going to come together now
entonces como que se van a juntar ahora
I don't like
varios contenidos no me gusta que se
several contents to come together but well that's
junten varios contenidos pero bueno es
what really happened I have a
lo que ha pasado realmente tengo un
video for the main channel that is
vídeo para el canal principal que está a
waiting for the thumbnail
la espera de de la miniatura
and and I have the newscast
y y tengo el noticiero a la espera
also waiting for the thumbnail and the editing
también de la miniatura y de la edición
and so on  so well in the meantime we're going to be
y demás entonces bueno de mientras vamos
here watching some videos what do you
a estar aquí viendo unos videítos qué os
think Oh really But how are you guys going to
parece Ay de verdad Pero cómo me vais a
be trying to play jokes on me
estar intentando gastarme bromas a mí
you [ __ ] but if you spend the whole
ustedes cabrones pero si estáis todo el
[ __ ] whole [ __ ] day treating me like an
[__] todo el [__] día tratándome como un
old man like I don't understand anything I'm trolling there
viejo como que no me entero de nada me
you laugh at me so
trole ahis os reís de mí entonces ya
every day it doesn't work [ __ ] I mean
todos los días no cuela cabrones O sea
one works
cuela uno
eh one works you know two not even because
eh uno cuela sabes dos incluso no porque
I'm a little clumsy but of course every
soy un poco torpe pero claro todos los
[ __ ] day it doesn't work the same joke
[__] dí no cuela la misma broma
make up another one about Who was the idea
inventar otra de Quién ha sido la idea
it's about Who was the idea Who was the
va de Quién ha sido la idea de Quién ha
idea how many views did
sido la ide cuánt visitas tuvo el
yesterday's news get 25000 things are getting really crazy
noticiero de ayer 25000 está la cosa se
things suddenly don't
ha carado mucho la cosa de repente no
get more things out a little bit suddenly it's
sacar má la cosa un poquillo de repente
not very calm no The little room
no está muy tranquilito no El salillo
Well this way Halloween lets us rest a little bit
Bueno así nos deja un poquito el
too because the
Halloween también descansar que la
truth is Look
verdad Mira
2963 members I [ __ ] on the m we're going
2963 miembros me cago en la m nos vamos
to play the
a tocar los
3000 I [ __ ] in the hand we're going to play
3000 me cago en la mano vamos a tocar
the 3000  Javi, about Chocas, I'm not going to watch
los 3000 Javi lo del chocas no voy a ver
anything else about Chocas anymore, it's because they
nada más del chocas nunca más es que se
upload late, but I saw it. Yes, I agree with you,
suben tarde pero lo vi sí ahí sí te doy
really. But look, it's also
la razón la verdad Pero mira también es
a bit of my fault. Let's see, blame. Yes, a bit of
un poco culpa a ver culpa Sí un poco
my fault too. Of course, if you give
culpa mía también Claro si tú le das a
the editors the videos at 8 in the
los Editores los vídeos a las 8 de la
evening, then they'll have them at the time they
tarde pues te lo van a tener a la hora
can. The poor things can't
que puedan los pobres tampoco pueden
do magic either, you know, but I get up in
hacer magia sabes pero yo me levanto por
the morning, I start compiling the
la mañana me pongo a recopilar las
news for the newscasts. And that's even though I
noticias para los noticieros Y eso que
have places in my area, I don't deserve it.
tengo a mi lugares que no me lo merezco
Eduardo, a kiss, welcome, Román has
Eduardo un beso bienvenido Román ha
given away 10, handsome. Thank you very much.
regalado 10 guapo Muchas gracias
But in the morning, in the morning, I
eh pero por la mañana por la mañana
try to compile
intento recopilar para noticiero Pin Pin
all the news for the newscast. Pin Pin Pin Pin, Luar, everything
Pin Pin todas las noticias luar todo lo
that he has sent me too, because Lu har
que me ha mandado también porque Lu har
is a
es una
machine. We upload the
máquina los clips de Twitter subimos los
shorts. Yes, I have a script for the
short eh si tengo algún guion para el
main channel. I have a video for the
canal principal tengo un vídeo para el
main channel that I should
canal principal que sí o sí debería
record tomorrow. Eh, yes, I should
grabarlo mañana Eh sí o sí debería
record it tomorrow. I have a video about
grabarlo mañana tengo un vídeo sobre el
Willy Red's game that I should record
juego de Willy Red que debería grabarlo
tomorrow. The thing is, I don't know if it's going to
mañana lo que pasa que no sé si ahora
work right now.  to work that much the
mismo va a funcionar eso mucho la
truth is I don't know if it's going to work much what do I do I do
verdad no sé si va a funciona mucho qué
it Are you going to support me if I upload it
hago lo hago lo Vais a apoyar si lo subo
or
o
not it's a video about Willy's game
no es un vídeo sobre el juego de Willy
No I haven't even reviewed the script yet and I
No no he repasado ni el guion todavía y
already know that I have to Add a
ya sé que le tengo que Añadir unas
few
cuantas de
things at least for the intro I have to
cosas por lo menos para la intro le
Add a few
tengo que Añadir unas cuantas de
things let's see you have to stir the
cosillas a ver hay que mover un poco la
hornet's nest a bit you know what Dana did Yeah let's see no
avispero viste lo de la Dana Sí a ver no
[ __ ] it I almost forgot to say it here
lo [__] casi se me olvida decirlo aquí
but because I come from telesalseo to
pero porque vengo de telesalseo en
telesalseo I have sent a hug to
telesalseo le he mandado un abrazo a
everyone but here Likewise
todo el mundo pero aquí Igualmente
send a hug to all of you who
mandaros Un abrazo a todos los que nos
are watching us from Valencia It's that here
estéis viendo de valencia Es que aquí
since I come at the wrong time I'm
como vengo a la hora golfa estoy
used to you being from or
acostumbrado a que seáis de o bien de
well from
latan bien de
North America selen das insulted shoka
Norteamérica selen das insultó al shoka
I don't give a damn as if he's [ __ ] his
me suda la [__] como si se [__] su
dog I mean I really don't care no I'm not
perro O sea que me da igual de verdad no
going to try anything more about
no voy a tratar más nada del
chocas [ __ ]
chocas [__]
Heavy what I said is worth a hug to all
Pesado lo dicho vale un abrazo para toda
the people from Valencia who are watching us
la gente de valencia que nos está viendo
I more or less the people  that I know from
yo más o menos la gente que conozco de
there I've been writing to them all
allí les he escrito ya durante todo el
day
día
and damn how strong how strong
y y [__] qué fuerte qué fuerte
natural catastrophe obviously that's what we are we're
catástrofe natural evidentemente es lo
nothing
que somos no somos nada
and these are things that
y son cosas
that happen suddenly no
que que que pasan de repente no muchas
thank you very much to all of you who are giving
gracias a todos los que estáis dando
members but what a welcome here every
miembros pero que recibimiento aquí cada
night it's a pleasure eh Lada Lada I've
noche da gusto eh Lada Lada le he
spoken to Of course today today I spoke
hablado Por supuesto hoy hoy he hablado
to Lada Yes today I spoke to Lada Oh
con lada Sí hoy he hablado con lada Uy
well I haven't written to uncle sh but I
pues no le he escrito al tío sh pero
think I haven't written to uncle shur
creo que no le he escrito al tío shur
Because because I saw a tweet no I mean
Porque porque he visto un tweet no O sea
uncle shur has posted something on Twitter
el tío shur ha puesto algo por Twitter
Well I haven't written to him man can you
Pues no le he escrito tío te puedes
believe I haven't written to uncle sh I
creer que no le he escrito al tío sh me
remembered Lada I haven't spoken to her for a
acordé de Lada que llevaba llevaba un
while without speaking to her true
tiempo sin hablar sin hablar con ella
we are each with our own
verd estamos cada uno l con nuestras
things and I think the last time I spoke
cosas y creo que la última vez que hablé
to her
con ella
was a collaboration we did on the
fue una colaboración que hicimos en el
main channel a few months ago with trine I
canal principal hace unos meses de trine
don't remember the asunta case I think it
no me acuerdo del caso asunta creo que
was and I remembered her directly
fue y me acordé de ella directamente
last night with what happened and I spoke to her and no she did
anoche con lo que pasó y le hablé y no
n't answer me last night and today I  I was
me no me contestó anoche y hoy me
worried because she answered and I called her
preocupé porque contestó y la llamé
nice to see you live
gustazo verte en vivo
cutie well the good thing about YouTube
guapura bueno lo bueno que tiene YouTube
is that you can always watch it also
es que lo podéis ver siempre también
reuploaded okay Ha but no more I will deal with
resubido vale Ja pero ya no Tratará
all the gossip what's up Angel from
todos los salseos qué va Ángel a partir
now on those of chocas banned okay I
de ahora los del chocas vetado vale he
saw that they announced the
visto que han anunciado los juegos del
squid games planned for the year
calamar previstos para el año
2025 auron will help the people IV no What's
2025 auron ayudará a la gente IV no Qué
wrong with IV now that he thinks he's cute
le pasa a IV ahora que se cree lindo
maybe he has more important things according to
acaso tiene cosas más importantes según
him that he leave his ego behind But what help
él que deje su ego Pero qué ayuda se
can be done I mean because
puede hacer o sea porque en plan no
I'm not very well informed In what type of
estoy muy muy puestos En qué tipo de
help can be given of course I mean I know
ayudas se pueden hacer claro o sea yo sé
that ivay has shared like that phone number
que ivay ha compartido como el teléfono
no that I put it on the news
ese no que lo he puesto en el noticiero
But what else can be done I mean in an
Pero qué más se puede hacer o sea en
economic way that economic there is something
plan económico eso económico hay algo
organized set up I imagine that it
organizado montado me imagino que eso
will take a series of days for them to
tendrán que pasar una serie de días para
make an assessment no Of
que para que hagan una valoración no
course you donate right now Who do you donate to I do
Claro tú ahora mismo donas A quién donas
n't understand
no entiendo
why ibai fixes the streets I think
que ibai arregle las calle yo creo que
ibai should fix a couple of
ibai debería arreglar un par de
neighborhoods But
barrios Pero
well what is Loc talking about Ah okay  auron
bueno De qué habla Loc Ah vale auron
wants to do something charitable Oh well look yes they
quiere hacer algo benéfico Ah pues mira
sent me something the thing is that of
s me mandaron algo lo que pasa es que
course In fact Karime sent it to me I think it
claro De hecho me lo mandó Karime creo
was Ah Karime no Who was it someone
fue Ah Karime no Quién fue alguien me
sent me something and he said Javi but you can't
mandó algo y me dijo Javi pero no puedes
participate no And I said [ __ ] well Ah look
participar no Y dije [__] pues Ah mira
yes
sí
Karime let's see what auron said Of
Karime a ver voy a ver lo que dijo auron
course if it's on twitter I can't
Es que claro si es en twit no puedo
Oh it's eliminated let's see I'll see I'll see
Oh está eliminado a ver voy a ver voy a
if I'll see if I can find the click
ver si voy a ver si encuentro el click
auron
auron
Valencia Aaron I put
Valencia Aarón he puesto
auron let's see like let's see what let's
auron a ver como a ver vamos a ver qué
see what auron said
vamos a ver qué es lo que ha dicho auron
the boss eh the boss is the one in charge have
el patrón eh el patrón es el que manda
you seen what happened in Valencia man how
has visto lo de valencia hombre como
could you not see it man how strong eh how
para no verlo tío qué qué fuerte eh qué
strong eh I mean it's very very very strong what
fuerte eh o sea es muy muy muy fuerte lo
happened eh eh for whoever it is
que ha pasado eh eh para el que sea
latan and all And I don't know Valencia is one of
latan y tal Y no sepa Valencia es una de
the most important cities in
las ciudades pues más importantes de
Spain no I mean at the level of the largest capitals
España no O sea a nivel de capitales más
no Valencia the the truth is
grandes no Valencia el el la verdad es
that there is Barcelona Seville Madrid
que está Barcelona Sevilla Madrid
Valencia no  Valencia would be one of the
Valencia no Valencia sería una de las
most important not most popular families
más importantes no familia más populares
and it turns out that well there is a river that
y resulta ser que bueno hay un río que
crosses in the middle that has been going on for a long time.
cruza por medio que ya hace un montonazo
Well, it
de décadas Pues
overflows with another meteorological situation
rebos con otra situación meteorológica
similar to the one now and then
parecida a la de ahora y y entonces pues
a lot of people died, a lot of people were left
murió mucha gente mucha gente se quedó
homeless and so on. This was many
sin casa y demás Esto hace muchísimas
decades ago, no, so at the time a
décadas no entonces en su momento
canal was created, a what do you call it? It's called an
se llama canal se llama un canal
assembly canal. What is it called, what would it be called that is to, to
ensamble Cómo se llama cómo se llamaría
retain, in other words, it's
que es para para para retener o sea es
like widening the, the a cause in base
como ensanchar el el el un cause en bse
no cause
no cause
cause for these floods
cause para est para estas inundaciones
so that they don't pass, no, so thanks to that
que no pasen no entonces gracias a ese
cause the city has been saved on this
cause se ha salvado la ciudad en esta
occasion, okay. But there was another one that
ocasión vale Pero había otro que no
wasn't as wide and so well-prepared
estaba también tan ancho y tan currado
that it has overflowed. So since the
que sí ha rebosado Entonces al haber
whole cause has overflowed, imagine
rebosado todo el caus imaginaros
crossing the entire south of Valencia, it
cruzando toda todo el sur de Valencia
has overflowed for all the
pues ha rebosado para todas las
neighborhoods and all the towns that it
barriadas y todos los pueblos a los que
has reached, it's tremendous. Okay, what's
ha alcanzado o sea tremendo Vale qué
happening? Well, a lot of people have died because they were
pasa pues que ha muerto mucha gente que
caught on the road, a lot of people who
le cogió en la carretera mucha gente que
maybe were caught going down to the garage
a lo mejor le cogió bajando al garaje
to get their car out. Well
para sacar el coche para fuera bueno
Well I've seen Juna's Twitter,
bueno he visto el Twitter de de juna
well Juna's Twitter, any
bueno el Twitter de juna cualquier
Twitter account now, I mean, you go
cuenta de Twitter ahora o sea te metes
on Twitter right now and all that
en Twitter ahora mismo y todo lo que
comes up is more or less
sale es más o menos es más o menos
videos and things of this kind that are
vídeos y cosas de de esto que son
tremendous, no, but look for example Juna
tremendas no pero mira por ejemplo juna
who is from Valencia, eh, has published some
que es de valencia eh ha publicado unos
videos of her neighborhood, Okay,
vídeos de su barrio Okay
Eh, This means that people are already
Eh Esto es que la gente ya está en plan
breaking loose, entering stores,
rompiendo entrando en las tiendas
taking televisions, anyway, this is already
llevándose televisores en fin esto ya es
crazy, okay, but look at this,
la locura desbocada vale pero Mirad esto
eh, I mean, during the whole
eh o sea durante toda la durante toda la
afternoon and evening yesterday. Well, imagine
tarde y la noche de ayer Pues imagínate
all these neighborhoods flooded. I
todos estos barrios inundados yo No
couldn't tell you the height. How high
sabría deciros la altura A qué altura
could the water be, for example, in a
podría estar el agua por ejemplo en un
neighborhood like this. I'm from Valencia. The
barrio como este yo soy de Valencia el
Turia hasn't overflowed, but the Cher.
turia no ha rebosado pero el y el Cher
Yes, and everything is flooded, of course. The Turia, I
Sí y está todo inundado claro el turia
understand that it is where they made the
entiendo que es en el que hicieron el
channel, this one that we talked about. No, I've
cauce este del que hemos hablado No yo
never been to Valencia, I've never
nunca he estado en Valencia nunca he
been. I've only been there by car
estado Solamente he pasado con el coche
on my way to Barcelona, ​​I think in my town it
para allá a Barcelona creo en mi pueblo
says quintuple, which is small in the  73 there
dice quintuple que es pequeño en el 73
were 89
hubo 89
deaths more than 2 Met areas of 2 Met
muertos más de 2 Met áreas de 2 Met
meter and a half 2 Met no I mean,
metro y medio 2 Met no O sea pues
imagine around here the cars eh
imaginaros por aquí los coches eh
floating I mean Clear Look at the cars
flotando o sea Claro Mira los coches
as they have appeared This is the neighborhood of
como han aparecido Este es el barrio de
juna clar Look at the cars as they have
juna clar Mira los coches como han
appeared clear the cars floating
aparecido claro los coches flotando
until the water has gone during
hasta que ya el agua se ha ido durante
the day the cars are floating pum p pum
el día los coches van flotando pum p pum
until they have been falling each one
hasta que ya han ido cayendo cada uno
when the water has gone not each one where
cuando el agua ha iddo no cada uno donde
the Where each one has fallen I mean how
la Donde ha caído cada uno O sea qué
awful and how scary What awful and
barbaridad Y qué miedo Qué barbaridad Y
how scary no then
qué miedo no entonces pues ha muerto
many people have died who perhaps had gone down
mucha gente que a lo mejor había bajado
to the garage to try to get the car
al garaje para intentar sacar el coche
out anyway that series of cars a
para fuera en fin esa serie de coche una
terrible tragedy I think that now until
tragedia terrible creo que ahora hasta
now what has been counted
ahora lo que hay contabilizado
confirmed are about 100
confirmado son unos 100
Dead What do you mean 400 joli what are you
Muertos Cómo que 400 joli a qué te
referring to now in telesalseo up to where we
refieres ahora en telesalseo hasta donde
were confirming it is understood that they are
estábamos confirmando se entiende que
more than 100 people for sure but
son más de 100 personas seguro pero
counted there were 90 and
contabilizado había 90 y
something in Seville also there was something
pico en Sevilla también habido algo
María José is that they
María José es que
give it
el la dan
after Valencia  like it was still
después de valencia como que todavía
continuing through Seville
continuaba por Sevilla
and and there's practically been
e y Y prácticamente ha habido
flooding not in Seville let's see in
inundaciones no en Sevilla a ver en
Seville there's been some let's see
Sevilla ha habido algún que otro a ver
the riverbed was almost overflowing okay from
estaba casi a rebosar el cauce vale por
what I've seen and there's been some damage
lo que he visto y ha habido algún daño
to some roads I think so yes or no
en alguna carretera creo que ha sí o no
but flooding I've only seen in the media
pero inundaciones yo en los medios nada
in
más que he visto en
jé which is like an hour and a half away
jé que está como a una hora y media A lo
Maybe from Seville no let's see everything that
mejor de Sevilla no a ver todo lo que es
the river is no I mean it's dangerous
el río no o sea es lo peligroso
let's say it's not rained all afternoon here it's
digamos aquí lleva toda la tarde sin
rained a lot these past few days
llover ha llovido mucho estos días atrás
but what it was in the afternoon I
pero lo que ha sido por la tarde yo
was like I had to go to the
estaba que tenía que ir a los
nutritionist And that uh Around
nutricionista Y eso
6 something I'd say it's stopped
las 6 y pico Yo diría que ya paró de
raining
llover
And how come someone has given him the
Y cómo que alguien le ha el
information someone has given him the information that there
dato que alguien le ha dado el dato de
are like 400 dead my goodness
que hay como 400 muertos madre mía madre
my goodness don't tell me that terrible how
mía no me digas eso terrible qué
apocalyptic a lot of encouragement from here to
apocalíptico mucho ánimo desde aquí a
all the people of Valencia man what's
toda la gente de valencia tío que
happened there is absolutely aberrant man
fte aberrante lo que ha ocurrido ahí tío
for those who don't know well there's been a
para el que no lo sepa pues ha habido un
storm called
temporal llamado
Dana
Dana
eh defined  like the cold drop an
eh definido como la gota fría un
absolutely horrible storm Well that has
temporal absolutamente horrible Pues que
caused
ha causado
floods well I'm sending some photos
inundaciones bueno mando unas fotos
of your town my goodness of
perchas de de su pueblo madre mía de
Christ I mean apocalyptic scene I mean
Cristo o sea escena apocalíptica o sea
cars piled up eh there have been several
coches amontonados eh ha habido varios
deaths I mean horrific the truth
fallecidos O sea horroroso la verdad
horrific So keep your spirits up and I wanted to
horroroso Así que mucho ánimo e quería
do something charitable I told
hacer algo benéfico se lo he dicho a
ibai but he's busy so let's see if I
ibai pero está ocupado así a ver si lo
can do it on my own Of course because I
puedo hacer por mi cuenta Claro porque
told i I say let's see if
le he dicho a i digo a ver si nos
you and I get together I don't know and we play
juntamos tú y yo yo que sé y jugamos a
[ __ ] I don't know We can do something
[__] no sé Podemos hacer como algo
charitable but he told me he has
benéfico pero me ha dicho que tiene
recordings I mean he can't I mean it's not that he does
grabaciones O sea no puede o sea no es
n't want to eh it's that he can't but
que no quiera él eh es que no puede pero
eh I don't know I can get together with someone else
eh No sé me puedo juntar con alguien más
and it can be done tomorrow or the day after Well there are
y se puede hacer mañana o pasado Bueno
days there are days ahead But it
hay días hay días por delante Pero
would be nice to do something something
estaría bien hacer algo algo algo
charitable It would also be nice to do it
benéfico También estaría bien hacerlo
when there is I mean it's good that it's not
cuando haya quiero decir es bueno que no
today but that there is some association
sea hoy sino que haya alguna asociación
or some [ __ ] like that to know what I
o [__] de estas para sab lo que te
want to tell you I think that for the moment I haven't
quiero decir creo que de momento no he
seen anything It's that we will have to
visto nada Es que eso habrá que
count who donates and how to donate and
contabilizar quién donar y cómo donar y
all the roll  look you asked me
todo el rollo a ver me habéis preguntado
Jai can you participate it's like I don't
Jai tú puedes participar es como yo que
know I can't participate with anyone in
sé yo no puedo participar con nadie en
anything on Twitch if they do it on Twitch
nada de Twitch si lo hacen en Twitch
well no but to the one that there is someone that is
pues no pero a la que haya alguna que
trustworthy Which I suppose will
que sea de confianza Que supongo que
be coming soon Eh well something can be done something
estará al caer Eh pues se podrá hacer
charitable Of course if I don't
algo algo benéfico Claro que sí si no lo
do it eh And I don't care I'll do it alone
hago yo eh Y me la pela lo hago yo solo
but well it's always good to have
pero bueno siempre está bien pues tener
the support of someone also big to be
el apoyo de alguien también grande para
able to do something like that no but
poder hacer alguna cosita así no pero
well no there won't be any problem Let's
bueno que no no habrá ningún problema A
see if we can do it in the next few
ver si lo podemos hacer los próximos
days
días
Eh And nothing much encouragement to all the people of
Eh Y nada mucho ánimo a toda la gente de
Valencia because it's absolutely
valencia porque es absolutamente de
crazy what's happened there eh
locos lo que ha pasado ahí eh
absolutely crazy
absolutamente de locos
man absolutely crazy have you
tío absolutamente de locos has
seen well we'll see well we'll see what
vist pues ya veremos pues ya veremos que
the old man organizes and
lo que organiza el viejo y
and whatever we're not going to see some
y en lo que sea no vamos a ver algunos
videos the truth Look I have here I have this
videítos la verdad Mira tengo aquí Este
video to watch for a few
vídeo para ver desde hace unos cuantos
days the divorce fate you have the
de días el divorcio fate tú tiene el
video already 700000 views two
vídeo ya 700000 visitas de hace dos
weeks ago the divorce did him good Hey
semanas el divorcio le hizo bien Oye
but it's not like Juan is changing
pero no es como que Juan está cambiando
even physically as a result of this  I ask I ask do
incluso físicamente a raíz de esto
n't you give us that
pregunto pregunto no da nos da usted esa
impression man lati there's a ra of
impresión hombre lati se viene una ra de
50 my chat
50 mi chat
of 50 my weapons what does that mean lauti
de 50 mi armas eso qué significa lauti
that you're going to give away 50 members or that
que vas a regalar 50 miembros o que
all of you who are here right now on
todos los que estáis ahora mismo aquí en
the live You're going to give away 50
el directo Vais a regalar 50
members did you see his video dressed as
miembros viste su vídeo disfrazado de
Pool Let's see Juan is not an
Pool A ver es que Juan no es una persona
ugly person he never has been yes it's true that like he did
fea nunca lo ha sido sí que es verdad
n't take care of himself all the time
que en plan no se cuidaba todo el tiempo
with the cap all the time with the glasses you
con la gorra todo el tiempo con la gafa
know then people there of course
sabes entonces pues la gente ahí claro
red chicken a kiss there are many times that
pollo rojo un beso hay muchas veces que
when you get married they come back to you less me not
cuando te casas te vuelven menos yo no
me Because I'm a flirt like ra told me
yo Porque soy un coqueto como me dijo ra
by the way What a slap
que por cierto Vaya [__] le ha pegado
unaf has given raed he has given him a slap let's
unaf a raed le ha pegado una [__] a
see but I don't know if I can put it I think so
ver pero no sé si la puedo poner creo
because I think I have it on
que sí porque creo que la tengo en
WhatsApp that a friend sent it to me he
WhatsApp que me la mandó una amiga la
gives him a huge slap that I say
pega una [__] descomunal que yo digo
this guy is stupid I mean he likes he likes it when he
este tío es tonto o sea le gusta le
hits him even the NF
gusta que le pegue hostias hasta la NF
of I mean he answers him from beds to
de o sea le contesta de camas a
camasutra from beds to camasutra he's the
camasutra de camas a camasutra es el
stud Hey that's going to be the title I
empotrador Oye ese va a ser el título
don't forget luar that title that I
que no se me olvide luar ese título que
liked from beds to stud
me ha gustado de camas a empotrador
says raet it seems to me a statement that
dice raet me parece un comunicado que
shows how intelligent you are ole
demuestra lo inteligente que eres ole
Look lauti has given away the 50 Hey
Mira lauti ha regalado los 50 Oye reto
50 challenge today lauti lauti poking people
de 50 hoy lauti lauti picando la peña
Well for now
Bueno pues de momento la [__] se la ha
lauti has taken out his dick if someone wants to take out their
sacado lauti si alguien quiere sacarse
ma they have to give away
la ma tiene que regalar
60 this is how the auction is going gentlemen find a
60 así está la subasta señores buscaros
way to see This will be a statement of
la vida a ver Esto será un comunicado de
this joke that raises the nter flay
esto de cachondeo que sube la nter flay
and says but you whitewash jav oliveira who
y dice pero blanqueas a jav oliveira que
lies like a scoundrel for defending
miente como un bellaco por defender a
Dallas the threesome hunter and puts a
Dallas el cazador de tríos y pone un
vampire emoji you suffered from
emoji de vampiro sufriste de amnesia
temporary amnesia from when he defended that the
temporal de cuando defendió que el
virolo was looking for a doxe art churra which is
virolo buscaba doxe arte churra que es
a mantra how stupid you are ra the truth is you
un mantra qué tonto eres ra la verdad
are a little stupid
eres un poco tonto
eh I don't even run into you nor you nor you nor I run into you friend I don't
eh Ni te topo ni te ni te topo amigo no
know anything about you I mean you started calling me
sé nada de ti o sea me empezaste a decir
dog I blocked you and little else you know
perro te bloqueé y y poco más sabes a
nauter FL they didn't want her do  ar doxing is
nauter FL no la querían do ar doxear es
like leaking your address Who is not
como filtrar su dirección Quién es no
leaking your data knowing who a
filtrar sus datos saber quién es una
person is to take legal action is
persona para tomar medidas legales pues
not doxing you understand that is something
no es un doxeo me entiendes eso es algo
that social networks should
que las redes sociales deberían
lend to the authorities and collaborate
prestarse a las autoridades y colaborar
which they do not do No I have already told you a
que no lo hacen No ya os contado un
million times I will continue to
millón de veces os lo seguiré
tell you that I am after a
contando que yo ando detrás de una
person who harasses me on social networks
persona que me acosa en redes sociales
with several multi-accounts and does not want to
con varias multicuenta y no me quiere
confirm justice Who it is But
confirmar la justicia Quién es Pero
because he does not feel like it Not because it is not possible okay
porque no le da la gana No porque no se
then nter fre says do you
pueda vale entonces nter fre dice te
think the tweet clicks and criticisms
parecen poco los tweet click y críticas
that I have dedicated to Javi are not enough, which
que le he dedicado a Javi que
can probably be counted by thousands
probablemente se puedan contar por miles
at what moment I am whitewashing him
en qué momento le estoy blanqueando
just in which I say that most of
justo en el que digo que la mayoría de
my criticism towards him is because he agrees with
mi crítica hacia él es porque le da la
Dallas in everything well This is
razón en todo a Dallas bueno Esto es
nafay confirming that the problem that
nafay confirmando que el problema que
the haters have with me is Dallas let's see
tienen conmigo los hater es Dallas a ver
now that Dallas is going to become a
ahora que el Dallas se va a volver un
whiter content okay let's see if now they
contenido más blanco vale a ver si ahora
let me No they let me a little
a mí me dejan No a mí me dejan un poco
too they will not get involved because of who I
también no se meterán por con quien me
take or who I defend or whatever  okay okay
lleve o por quien defienda o lo que sea
I'm aware of who each one is
vale soy consciente de quién es cada uno
and Dallas is a psychopath that I've been
y Dallas es un psicópata al que llevo
exposing for years And you are a scammer and
años exponiendo Y tú eres un estafador y
an abuser, they have exposed you in 1
un maltratador te han expuesto de 1
ways and I'm not talking about Dallas not because
formas y no hablo de Dallas no porque
now you go against Dallas I'm going to
ahora vayas en contra de Dallas Voy a
give you validation I don't hang out with the
darte validación yo no me junto con la
garbage Well although I don't agree
basura Pues aunque no estoy de acuerdo
with what Dallas says obviously RAE
con lo que dice Dallas evidentemente RAE
you're going to be papped you're going to be papped by a
te vas papeado te vas papeado por un
hater you're
hater vas buscando
always looking for the comport in the same way my
la siempre comport de la misma forma mi
wife eye that dubbing of the roosters that I have
esposa ojo que doblaje de los gallos que
n't seen you for a long time king
hacía mucho tiempo que no te veía rey
How are you They gave me a few days off
Cómo estás Me han dado unos días libres
at work because of Valencia tomorrow I
en el trabajo por lo de valencia mañana
don't get up early and it's been a while since I saw you
no madrugo y hacía tiempo que no te veía
live I'm glad to see you here
en directo Me alegro de verte por aquí
friend I wish it had been for another reason
amigo Ojalá hubiera sido por otro motivo
too I say a kiss a kiss
también te digo un beso un beso
handsome 60 members says the auti that
guapo 60 miembros dice el auti que no
nobody has the balls to
tiene nadie [__] a
give away with almost 2000 people here
regalar habiendo aquí casi 2000 personas
my sea la is going to be the one in charge here today
mi sea la va a ser aquí el que manda hoy
in the chat I
en el chat lo
doubt it
dudo
Congratulations Congratulations beds
Felicidades Felicidades camas
Congratulations c a so we won't forget  your
Felicidades c a así no olvidaremos tus
cadadas a video Hey but Lauti has
cadadas un vídeo Oye pero lauti ha
given away another 50 that's 100 now Lauti you're not
regalado ot 50 ya son 100 ya lauti no
going to let anyone get angry no one is
vas a dejar a nadie que se pique nadie
going to be able to give away more than 100 members I
va a poder regalar más de 100 miembros
see it as very very very
lo veo muy muy muy
complicated very complicated
complicado muy complicado
eh very very very complicated man the other
eh muy muy muy complicado tío el otro
day I ate a
día me comí un
bite the other day I ate a
bite el otro día me comí un
bite
bite
[Music]
[Música]
with this click that you just saw
con con este click que acabáis de ver
as if Juan had reacted or rather they
como que Juan había reaccionado o sea es
set it up perfectly and the clip came out on
que lo montaron perfecto y me salió en
Twitter and I put it on the
Twitter el clip y lo puse en el
news and I published the news and it
noticiero y lo publiqué el noticiero y
put me between Javi that that has never
me puso la entre Javi que eso no ha
happened in my life or they set it up
pasado en la vida o se lo montaron
perfectly with Juan reacting to that clip
perfecto a Juan reaccionando a ese clip
and there comes a moment when his
y llega un momento en el que le cambia
face changes Yeah I know two weeks went by I do
la cara Sí ya sé que pasaron dos semanas
n't remember when it is when they
no me acuerdo en qué momento es cuando
call him Cook Maybe when they call him
le dicen Cook A lo mejor cuando le dicen
Cook I think the smile disappears I
Cook creo que se le borra la sonris O
mean and and thank goodness that as soon as we put it up
sea y y menos mal que nada más que lo
two or three people left me some comments Javi no that that
gente dos o tres Javi que no que que eso
's trolling damn it to me  I ate man we
es un troleo [__] me lo comí tío nos lo
ate it running I deleted them we
comimos corriendo los borré los
retouched the news we uploaded it with
retocamos el noticiero lo subimos con
other
otras
news I saw that newscast when it came out
noticias vi ese noticiero cuando salió
The good thing is that it didn't last long man
Lo bueno es que no duró mucho hombre
we try to be
intentamos ser lo
as truthful as possible you understand But
más veraz posible me entiendes Pero
well in the end I am a human I am a
bueno al final soy un humano soy un
human I already understood They didn't hate me they
human Ya lo entendí No me odiaban a mí
hated my
odiaban a mi
wife
esposa
fel 50 members out there over there I am
fel 50 miembros por ahí por ahí lo estoy
seeing it in the chat now it will appear on
viendo en el chat ahora saldrá en
screen but there peck there peck there peck it's
pantalla pero ahí pique ahí pique ahí
gone he has given away another 50 kid Dad scales Congratulations Cook even so we will not forget your falls juen Yes I know that two weeks have passed since everyone started talking about this but it's that my friend the beds or rather Now he is on a diet he is fine he looks very
Ahora es diet está fino se le ve muy
good and he simply had to grow a
bien y simplemente tuvo que dejarse la
beard and divorce giving Gameplays
barba y divorciarse de dar Gameplays
to instantly become more handsome
para hacerse instantáneamente más guapo
than he was not and I think he made the
de lo que no era y creo que tomó la
right decision I mean he hasn't been the
decisión correcta O sea no ha sido el
only one who has done it this year I mean I already
único que lo ha hecho este año o sea ya
did it Juan when he separated from me
lo hizo yo Juan cuando se separó de mii
and Juan pushed my crazy
y Juan le pegado un empujón a mi loco
man because he's living the dream he lives off
tío porque está viviendo el sueño vive
playing video games and being sued
de jugar videojuegos y de ser demandado
by Nintendo and so did auron
por Nintendo y también lo hizo auron
Play who left good Bin they gave me
Play que dejó a bueno Bin me han dado
a few days off at work because of
unos días libres en el trabajo por lo de
Valencia tomorrow I'm not getting up early and it's been a
valencia mañana no madrugo y hacía
while since I saw you live everything
tiempo que no te veía en directo todo
has its good side I'm glad to see you
tiene su lado bueno Me alegra verte por
here handsome that then he was with
aquí guapísimo que luego estuvo con
gemita for a short time and they separated anyway
gemita un corto tiempo y se separó igual
and although in the middle of both breakups there was
y Aunque en medio de ambas rupturas Hubo
a lot of hate in between Nothing compares to
mucho hate de por medio Nada se compara
the divorce of arig gaml and Juan guarnizo
el divorcio de arig gaml y Juan guarnizo
because in itself it was already the most
porque ya de por sí era en la pareja más
hated couple on the entire Latin American internet
odiada de todo internet hispanoamericano
because it made a lot of people have
Porque hizo que mucha gente tuviera
mixed feelings there was a part
Sentimientos encontrados hubo una parte
of the people who said that Juan
de las personas que decían que Juan
guarnizo was finally free from AR
guarnizo por fin era libre de AR
Gameplays and there was another side that was
Gameplays y Había otro lado que estaba
criticizing ar Gameplay because after
criticando a ar Gameplay porque luego de
announcing his divorce he was taking a
anunciar su divorcio estaba tomando un
flight to Spain and we already know who is
vuo hacia España y ya sabemos quién está
there anyway when they
allá de todas maneras cuando se
divorced Juan guarnizo looked
divorciaron a Juan guarnizo se le notaba
very very sad he was a man who had
muy muy triste era un hombre que había
lost the most important thing which is his life
perdido lo más importante que es su vida
his bed I have some news that is not
su cama tengo una noticia que no es
pretty for many it's going to  be shock Ari and
bonita para muchos va a ser choque Ari y
I made the decision to
yo hace semanas tomamos la decisión de
get divorced weeks ago what an exclusive we
divorciarnos pedazo de exclusiva que
gave here eh here I didn't give it on my
dimos aquí eh aquí no lo di en mi canal
main channel what an exclusive we gave
principal pedazo de exclusiva que dimos
eh what an exclusive eh those of you who are
eh pedazo exclusiva eh los que estáis
subscribed to Javi Oliveira and to La
suscritos a Javi oliveira y a la
Salsería find out Always before
salsería os enteris Siempre antes de
everything man months before eh months before How I
todo tío meses antes eh meses antes Cómo
told this the day before I could have
conté esto el día antes lo pudo haber
told it two or three days before but I
contado dos o tres días antes pero me
remember that there was like a little mess do
acuerdo que hubo como una pequeña liada
you remember that I was going to tell it the
os acordáis que lo iba a contar la
first night here and there was like a
primera noche aquí y hubo como una
little mess and they stopped me and I don't know what
pequeña liada y me frenaron y no sé qué
came out nonsense and then finally I
saale tonterías y luego finalmente lo
told it the next day on the
conté al día siguiente en el canal
main channel and then the thing about Juan
principal y luego lo del tema de de Juan
no, the thing about Gemita's horns
no lo del tema de los cuernos de gemita
and all that stuff also exclusive to
y todo el rollo ese también exclusivo
the main channel not all the horns
del Canal principal no todos los cuernos
that Gemita puts and her customs are not
que pone gemita y sus costumbre no son
her customs and we have to respect them it has
sus costumbres y tenemos que respetarlas
been a complicated decision but
ha sido una decisión complicada pero se
the truth has been told in a very
ha llevado la verdad de manera muy
healthy way and in a very How to say it
saludable y de manera muy Cómo decirlo
very calmly the truth and
con mucha calma la verdad y fuera de
joking aside all the hate they received was not
bromas todo el hate que recibían no era
so deserved I mean yes it was  a good
tan merecido O sea sí era una buena
way to farm views being a youtuber
manera de farmear vista siendo youtuber
but really you shouldn't take it
pero realmente no había que tomárselo
so personally because it wasn't that serious an issue I
tan personal porque no era un tema tan
think the most questionable thing that
grave creo que lo más cuestionable que
Juan Guarnizo did was try to do
hizo el Juan guarnizo fue intentar hacer
a Minecraft event and pretend to
un evento de Minecraft y pretender
pay the streamers who participated
pagarle a los streamers que participaran
with exposure and most likely with
con exposición y muy probablemente con
pizzas well there were no pizzas but let's see
pizas bueno no hubo pizas pero a ver
with me Juan for me let's see for me
conmigo el Juan para m a ver para m el
Juan behaved badly with me with me for
Juan se portó mal conmigo conmigo para
me he behaved
mí se portó
badly he made me very ugly compared
mal me hizo un feo muy grande respecto
to the rest of the gossip channels here we
al resto de canales de salseo aquí lo
saw it live no and I got
vimos en directo no y me cabreé un
really pissed off he actually wrote to me while
montón él me escribió de hecho mientras
I was there exploding but well I did
que yo estaba ahí explotando pero bueno
n't want to talk to him sincerely
no quise hablarle sinceramente es que
things don't happen when you want them to or
las cosas no son cuando uno quiera o
when things happen when we both want them
cuando las cosas cuando queramos los dos
but well there are things that not everything is
pero bueno hay cosas que no todo es
Ari's fault Yes well he has been unfaithful he has his
de Ari Sí bueno ha sido infiel tiene sus
issues no but but Juan has had his
movidas no pero pero Juan ha tenido sus
ups and downs okay I mean people
más y sus menos vale o sea que la gente
obviously change and people Ok
cambia evidentemente y que la gente Ok
whatever he wants is okay but Juan
todo lo que quiera vale pero que Juan
has his thing for me with Auron he
tiene su cosilla para mí con auron se
behaved badly Auron is the one who has
portó mal auron es el que le ha
forgiven and he will know even d it hurt him it didn't
perdonado y él sabrá hasta d le dolió no
hurt him okay but
le dolió vale pero
man, let's see it wasn't all his fault
hombre a ver no era todo culpa
if it had been a minimum wage job it
si hubiese sido un trabajo de sueldo
most likely would have happened they
mínimo muy probablemente Hubiese pasado
were going to pay them with experience and
iban a pagarles con experiencia y
obviously we couldn't leave behind the
obviamente no podíamos dejar atrás la
best donation of all time that
mejor donación de todos los tiempos la
of the a I'm going to give a I'm going to give a
de la a mí voy a dar un voy a dar una un
Popular opinion let's see what you say Okay yes it
Popular opinón a ver qué me decís Ok sí
is true that there is like
que es verdad que hay como
certain approval in fact it
cierto como cierta aprobación de hecho
seems to me that they just gave away another
me parece que acaban de regalado otros
50 members they are not the same as before it's like it's
50 miembros no son lo mismo de antes hay
true it is very applauded that
cierto se aplaude mucho el hecho de que
when a
cuando un
man breaks up a relationship well not that
hombre rompe una relación bueno no que
the man breaks it up but whatever a
la rompa el hombre sino lo que sea una
relationship ends That the man
relación se termina Que el hombre de
suddenly starts taking care of himself, going to the
repente empiece a cuidarse a ir al
gym, his Prime comes I don't know what I don't know
gimnasio se viene su Prime no sé qué no
how much it seems a little like that to me e Let's see, I'm
sé cuánto me parece un poco eso e A ver
not going to say machismo, I'm not going to pull on
no voy a decir machismo no voy a tirar
machismo okay But like of course
del machismo vale Pero como claro o sea
now when you see when you see that they
ahora cuando te ves cuando te ves que te
left you So now you take care of yourself Hey
han dejado Entonces ahora te cuidas Oye
kid Take care of yourself always look
chico Cuídate siempre
good for yourself, for your wife too,
está guapo para tu para tu mujer también
not first for yourself, first
no lo primero para ti mismo lo primero
for yourself but  well if you don't care about
para ti mismo pero bueno si a ti te da
taking care of yourself and you're one of those who leaves
igual cuidarte y eres de lo que te deja
the afro there in the balls Okay Take care of yourself they
lo afro ahí en los [__] Vale Cuídate
always have to leave you or they have to
siempre te tienen que dejar o te tienen
cheat on you so you
que poner los cuernos para que te
start taking care of yourself [ __ ] always take care of yourself
empieces a cuidar cabrón cuídate siempre
Always take care of yourself and it's like now not these
Cuídate siempre y es como ahora no estos
videos that are in fashion in the last few
vídeos que están est en las últimas
hours not the gl of Juan
horas muy de moda no el gl de Juan
Guarnizo that then we'll see another one Yeah yeah of
guarnizo que luego vamos a ver otro Sí
course it's like [ __ ] Juan has improved
sí claro es como [__] Juan ha mejorado
Juan has improved since he's not been with
Juan ha mejorado desde que no está con
Ari Of course because they've cuckolded him Now he
Ari Claro porque le han cuckeado Ahora
sees himself alone and he takes off his cap and he
se ve solo y se quita la gorrita y se
takes off his glasses and now he starts to
quita la gafita y ahora se pone a
take care of himself and he's thinner
cuidarse y está más delgado se pone
Okay of course why Ari hasn't improved
Bueno claro por qué Ari no ha mejorado
when she broke up with Juan Well he hasn't
cuando lo ha dejado con Juan Pues no ha
improved because he already took care of himself and because he
mejorado porque ya se cuidaba y porque
was already well It's like you applaud the one who
ya estaba bien Es como se aplaude al que
was leaving because he was tired
estaba dejándose porque estaba cansado
because he was married Sorry more than
porque estaba casado Perdón más que
because he was married
porque estaba casado
and now it's like you don't have to work hard
y ya como que no te lo tienes que currar
Hey boy boy boy boy boy
Oye chico chico chico chico chico
boy you have to shave your
chico hay que depilarse la
armpit you have to leave
axila hay que dejarse
that okay I mean like you have to take care of yourself  as
eso vale o sea en plan hay que cuidarse
long as it's very good Look for your
siempre que está muy bien Buscar tu
Prime then no because of course then you have to
Prime luego no porque claro luego te
look for the big life boy
tienes que buscar la vidorra chico lo
what can't happen is that
que no lo que no puede pasar es que
you're 25 years old and you're looking like
tengas 25 años y te estés dejando como
a 60 year old gentleman who shouldn't
un caballero de 60 que tampoco de 60 hay
look 60 either eh I've always said it
que dejarse eh yo ya siempre lo he dicho
my goal is that when I'm 60
yo mi objetivo es que cuando yo tenga 60
years old I'm going to be like Brad Pit or like
años voy a llegar como Brad Pit o como
Jesús Basque I don't accept
Jesús basque no acepto
minimum bed and honestly That was the
mínimo cama y sinceramente Esa fue la
worst answer that could have been given I don't think
peor respuesta que pudo haber dado Creo
anyone had ever said it but if
que nunca nadie lo había dicho pero si
I had been Juan Guiz I would have
yo hubiese sido Juan guiz hubiese
answered something like Oh yeah you have to
respondido algo como Oh sí tú tienes que
pay 3.99 to see her I sleep with her
pagar 3.99 para verla yo duermo con ella
every day and that's it she eats everything and
todos los días y listo se papea todo y
it was like a chat t What a good
quedaba como un chat t Qué buena
answer that was I try to be a
respuesta era esa yo trato de
competition churra My worst enemy is the
competencia churra Mi peor enemigo es la
lordship a kiss to telesalseo and to the
señoria un beso a telesalseo y a los
churras of the salseria today the gentlemen
churras de la salseria hoy la señoreros
very powerful today the gentlemen members
muy potente hoy la señoreros miembros
We've been here so far this night for 168
Llevamos aquí en lo que va de noche 168
well let's see the gentlemen powerful and they
bueno a ver la señoreros potente y
gave away a hundred and some members okay
regalaron cient y pico de miembros vale
And well then the auti  it's that we didn't
Y bueno pues la auti es que no
count on you here today the truth is we didn't
contábamos contigo hoy aquí la verdad no
count on you Ho here but it sounds a
contábamos contigo Ho aquí pero queda un
little better and you don't have to give the answer
poco mejor y no ten que dar la respuesta
that he gave as a typical Spider-Man fan
que dio de típico fan de spider-man
time to see the redit Per let's see
tiempo de ver el el redit Per veamos
quickly But why didn't it come out he got
rápid Pero por qué no le salió se quedó
cut off Look for me here this moment
cortado Mira para mí aquí este momento
of Juan's is the
de Juan es la
sign for me this moment of Juan's is the
señal para mí este momento de Juan es la
sign that Juan was
señal de que a Juan le
affected Ari's only fan his name was
afectaba el only fan de Ari se llamaba
another way Prip I think okay but it
de otra manera Prip creo vale pero le
affected him he wanted to give it an
afectaba él quería dársela de mentalidad
open mind that I don't care that my
abierta de que no me importa que mi
wife does this no guys no no no no I've
mujer haga esto no chicos no no no no yo
always said it I really respect
lo he dicho siempre yo respeto mucho a
everyone who does it okay because
todo el mundo que lo haga vale porque
obviously you're not hurting
evidentemente no le estás haciendo daño
anyone but of course if you're
a nadie pero claro si se lo estás
doing it to your partner if you're
haciendo a tu pareja si se lo estás
doing it to someone I respect that
haciendo a alguien Yo respeto que todo
everyone who wants to do that should do it
el mundo que quiera hacer eso que lo
you want to create a website
haga te quieres crear una página web
where you sell your naked photos that's
donde vender tus fotos en pelotas está
perfect I mean you can do
perfecto O sea tú puedes hacer con tu
whatever you want with your body
cuerpo lo que tú quieras
but I wouldn't do it nor would I put up with
pero yo no lo haría ni ni yo aguantaría
any of my partner doing it
que ninguna pareja mía lo
sincerely I don't want anyone to
sinceramente no quiero que nadie se
jerk off with my partner What do you want  I'm
pajee con mi pareja Qué quieres que te
telling you, I prefer to reserve that privilege
diga prefiero reservarme ese privilegio
for myself, you know, and I
para mí sabes y algunas partes de la
also prefer to reserve some parts of intimacy
intimidad también prefiero reservá melas
for myself, and if my partner has to
para mí y que si mi pareja tiene que
turn someone on with dancing,
calentar a alguien con bailes con
postures, or whatever, it should be
posturas o lo que sea que sea
exclusively for me, I mean, we're
exclusivamente a mí o sea lo estamos
selling absolutely everything, nowadays there's no longer any
vendiendo absolutamente todo hoy en día
respect for anything, a
no ya no se tiene respeto por nada un
kiss, Seba, I don't know if it's new or if it's from a
beso seba no sé si es nuevo o es el de
friend, but a kiss. But if you
ante amigo pero un beso Pero si tú lo
want to do it perfectly, I mean, if you
quieres hacer perfecto O sea si tú lo
want to do it and you both agree to do it
quieres hacer y estáis de acuerdo en
perfectly, [ __ ] great, eh. I think it's
hacerlo perfecto de putísima madre eh Me
great. You can do whatever you
parece genial podéis hacer lo que
want. Now, if tomorrow
queráis ahora bien si el día de mañana
you have
tienes
children in school, they're going to send them
hijos en el colegio le van a mandar las
photos of their mother jumping photos and
fotos de su madre saltando fotos y
HD videos. Today it is recorded very well. You
vídeos HD a día de hoy se graba muy bien
have to keep that in mind, not your
Hay que tener en cuenta eso no a tu
father. If you have a father who is
padre si tienes un padre que está
still active, not young, who
todavía en el activo no joven que se
finds out about things and who surfs the
entera de las cosas y que navega por
internet, when they want to mess with
internet cuando se quieran meter con
her and hurt her, they're going to send him
ella y hacerle daño le van a mandar
photos of his daughter in fishnet stockings
fotos de su hija con unas medias de red
and a thong that covers the slit in your
y con un tanga que te tapa la raja de tu
skirt, that's
falda
all pretty, well, for me
solamente está bonito eso pues para mí
No well for me No I'm not going to act all
No pues para mí No yo no me las voy a
modern it doesn't matter you understand
dar de moderno de da igual me entiendes
something else
otra cosa
eh what does my places send me
eh qué me manda mi
Ah I have to look at that topic
lugares Ah es que tengo que ver ese tema
then tomorrow I'll look at it since today no no I can't
luego mañana lo miro ya que ya hoy no no
heat my mind any more but I'll
no puedo calentar más mi mente pero lo
look at it now
miro ahora
eh And apart from that with the Lifan issues
eh Y aparte con esos temas de los lifan
I think it's quite proven
yo creo que queda bastante demostrado
that one
que ocurre una
thing happens what happens with those
cosa lo que ocurre con esos temas de los
Lifan issues is
lifan es
that in the end you say no but it's that I'm going to
que al final tú dices no pero es que voy
earn a lot of money I don't care
a ganar muchísimo dinero me da igual
okay because I'm seeing compensated that
vale porque estoy viendo compensado que
I'm a millionaire so laugh at me my
soy millonario entonces rí de mí mi
father my father I took him away from work
padre mi padre lo quitado yo de trabajar
and bought him a mansion and he doesn't give a damn
y le comprar una mansión y se la suda
seeing me naked my son is not even
verme en pelota a mi hijo mi hijo ni se
going to find out because tomorrow we're
va a enterar porque el día de mañana nos
going to move to the United States and my
vamos a mudar a los Estados Unidos y mi
son is going to study in a school that that that that
hijo va a estudiar en un colegio que que
is contrary to what you want
que que es contrario lo que tú quieras
okay but the thing is that there are going to be more people
vale pero es que va a haber más gente
who are going to have it for free than paying I mean that has
que lo va a tener gratis que pagando o
been completely
sea eso ha quedado completamente
proven that it is uncontrollable that there are
demostrado que es incontrolable que haya
people who have it for free someone hasn't
gente que lo tenga gratis alguien no ha
seen
visto a
Ari someone here hasn't seen
Ari alguien aquí no ha visto a
Ari today  a girl who
Ari hoy se retiró una chica que en 3
earned 67 million in ol fan retired Of course
años ganó 67 millones en ol fan Claro
luar but
luar pero
how many How many are there like that there are a few I
cuántas Cuántas hay así hay unas cuantas
know you sleep well knowing that your wife is
sé duermes bien sabiendo que tu mujer es
a sexual object these wankers from chat
un objeto sexual estos pajeros del chat
molbo her and her pack gets up for free
la molbo an y su pack se levanta gratis
on the
en
internet I sleep he does
internet duermo
n't know what to answer that he is left out he is left out I put together
no sabe qué responder que se queda
very well in a bed very
cortado armo muy bien en una cama muy
surely much more expensive than yours much
seguramente mucho más cara que la tuya
more comfortable in a house much more
mucho más cómoda en una casa mucho más
beautiful than yours it cringe the
bonita que la tuya da cringe la
answer with a woman much more beautiful
respuesta con una mujer mucho más bonita
than yours and a family much more
que la tuya y una familia mucho más
beautiful than yours story Final Point
linda que la tuya historia Punto Final
a big hug on the other hand I
un abrazo grande por el otro lado no se
can't forget that the title of this
me puede olvidar que el título de este
boo the guy or the thumbnail of the
buo el tío o la miniatura del
beds of beds of
camas de
beds to
camas de de camas a
camasutra but I don't know if that will be understood
camasutra pero no sé si se va a entender
not from beds to camasutra that will be understood
eso no de camas a camasutra se entenderá
Gameplay and Juan guarnizo
eso Gameplay y Juan guarnizo se
met in the worst possible way through
conocieron de la peor manera posible por
Twitter in 2015 and at that
os de Twitter en el 2015 y para ese
time ar gam already had a boyfriend
momento ar gam ya tenía un novio que se
named akim Aguilar who is a
llamaba akim Aguilar que es un youtuber
very  famous at least from that time and Juan
muy famoso al menos de esa época y Juan
What else has happened to Juan to kin Aguilar
Qué más le ha ido a Juan a kin Aguilar
this eh I mean he was very famous at the time
este eh o sea fue muy famoso en la época
but eh his channels died the truth
pero eh falleció sus canales la verdad
Well I don't know how he is doing today
Bueno no sé a día de hoy cómo le irá
but his channels died only cuqueo Yes
pero falleció sus canales solo cuqueo Sí
the cuado cuqueo to someone else and I could
el cuado cuqueo a alguien más y podría
say that akim is the supreme cook because
decir que akim es el cook supremo porque
arig left him for Juan guarnizo and since
arig lo dejó por Juan guarnizo y como
Juan guarnizo was already quite famous
Juan guarnizo ya era bastante famoso
at that time arl who was
para ese momento arl que estaba en
growing in numbers on the internet he was
crecimiento en números en el internet se
accused of being a house Partner
le acusaba de ser una casa Partner
you know people insult me ​​in a
ustedes saben la gente me insulta de una
very special way that I don't know they call me
manera muy especial que no sé me ponen
house Partner for having
el nombre de casa Partner por haber
had a boyfriend who is a youtuber
tenido un novio que es youtuber más
bigger than me with more views clearly and for
grande que yo con más views claramente y
having ended up because
por haber terminado por haber terminado
he ended up with me I am the one who is left I am the one who is
él conmigo yo soy la que quedo yo soy la
left wrong The truth is that I do not know what to
que quedo mal La verdad es que no sé qué
tell you about the subject in truth I
decirles sobre el tema en verdad les
promise you that it has been the most difficult thing since I
prometo que ha sido lo más difícil desde
ended my relationship with akim because
que terminé mi relación con akim porque
people do not take me down from that and it seems
la gente no me baja de eso y me parece
quite unfair to me that relationship had already been
bastante Injusto esa relación ya había
born in the middle  of the controversy but they
nacido en medio de la polémica pero
were pretty calm except for those who
estaba bastante tranquilos salvo por ahí
made memes and that Juan
que les hacían memes y que a Juan
Guarnizo was called Cook even
guarnizo lo trataban de Cook incluso
before the bed meme ar Gameplays
antes del Meme de la cama ar Gameplays
was the one that really brought problems
era la que realmente traía los problemas
to the relationship like when she fought with
a la relación como cuando se peleaba con
windy girk because she had surgery that
windy girk porque estaba operada que
showed a lot and in the end the two had
mostraba mucho y al final las dos tenían
only fans it was literally a fight of disabled people
only fans era una pelea de inválidos
and after sending the
literalmente y luego de mandar al
Archangel Gabriel to punish the
Arcángel Gabriel Para que castigara a la
sinner Ari Gameplays windy Gear was
pecadora Ari Gameplays windy Gear se
able to redeem herself and in the end she is living
pudo redimir y al final está viviendo
peacefully or well I don't know what she's
tranquila o bueno no sé qué está
doing let's see wend eh she sank she
haciendo a ver wend eh se hundió
could have been very rich too and
pudo haber sido muy millonaria también y
very and continue to triumph today
muy y seguir a día de hoy triunfando sin
however eh something happened to windy that
embargo eh a windy le pasó una cosa que
happens to few people but it happens to some
a poca gente le pasa pero le pasa alguna
And that is that
Y es que el
hatred consumes her and hatred ends up
odio le consume y y el odio se acaba
becoming
convirtiendo
the center
en el centro
of the center of her life or rather, for
de el centro de su vida o sea yo por
example, I am here and for me right now
ejemplo estoy aquí y para mí ahora mismo
my priority the center of my work is to
mi prioridad el centro en mi trabajo es
earn
ganar
money Okay, earn money, improve the
pasta Okay ganar pasta mejorar la
quality, making the best content
calidad ir haciendo el mejor contenido
that corresponds to each possible channel
que corresponda en cada canal posible
okay And  I can
okay Y yo por medio pues puedo tener
fight Victoria Thank you very much, welcome
pelea Victoria Muchas gracias bienvenida
beautiful Can I fight with someone? I
guapísima puedo pelearme con alguien
can fight, you know, but these are
puedo pelearme sabes pero son
arguments that happen here on
discusiones que son van pasando por aquí
the side fum fum fum fum but there are
por el lado fum fum fum fum pero hay
many times, well, many, not a few But
muchas veces bueno muchas no pocas Pero
some of us have seen how suddenly
algunas hemos visto como de repente
someone who could have it all here at
alguien que puede tenerlo todo aquí en
work focuses and becomes
el trabajo se se enfoca y convierte en
the non-springboard,
el no trampolín
no, their entire life is catapulted only
no su vida entera se catapulta solamente
from hatred for a person or a conflict they've
del odio a una persona o a un conflicto
had and
que haya tenido y
then that leads them to
entonces eso le lleva a
sink, that leads them to join, we've
hundirse eso le lleva a unirse lo hemos
seen it in many, in some cases, we
visto en muchos en algunos casos lo
've seen it in several okay and Windy was
hemos visto en varios vale y windy fue
a case, she became obsessed with the ar
un caso se obsesionó con el tema ar
Gameplay issue, it became a
Gameplay se se convirtió en un tema
central issue in her life
central en su vida vale y priorizó el
okay and she prioritized the hatred she has and it doesn't let her, it doesn't let her, it doesn't let her live, damn, he's a God, really and we go back two weeks ago when ar Gameplays and Juan Guarnizo announced their divorce, no, it's that
guarnizo anunciaron su divorcio no en es
with that donation, the
que con esa donación no funcionaba lo de
you pay thing didn't work and I shouldn't have said,
tu pagas y yo no tenía que haber dicho
you keep the photos and videos, I
ustedes quédense las fotos y videos yo
enjoy the
me disfruto la Fuente
original source, for example, it's also a
original por ejemplo también es una
good answer handsome same Stream but
buena respuesta guapo mismo Stream sino
each one on their own by that time they had been
cada uno por su lado ya para ese momento
separated for a while and they had
ya llevaban un tiempo separados y
simply made it public eh
simplemente lo habían hecho público eh
among other things chat well I would like to
entre otras cosas chat pues me gustaría
share with you that Ju What will happen with pambi
compartirles que Ju Qué pasará con pambi
what the [ __ ] do I know Armando I saw like suddenly
yo qué [__] sé Armando vi como que de
uploaded no no boo yeah I don't know the truth I don't know the
subió no no bu sí no lo sé la verdad no
truth I have to make a video
sé la verdad tengo que hacer un vídeo
of Will's game that yes I
del juego de Will eso sí lo
know yes we are separating I will tell you
sé sí nos estamos separando les diré
like the most
como lo más
important thing when an
important cuando un
event Thank you the Sub I am going to tell you the
eventi Gracias la Sub les voy a decir lo
most important thing which is because Wind has
más importante que es porque Wind ha
disappeared we are all to see are you
desaparecido estamos todos a ver estáis
listening to the video what are you
escuchando el vídeo que estáis
making are you listening to the video let's see
haciendo estáis escuchando el vídeo a
confirm me in the chat Yes yes yes Javi
ver confirmarme en el chat Sí sí sí Javi
is very handsome are you watching the video or
está muy guapo estáis viendo el vídeo o
are you each on your own [ __ ] roll
estáis cada uno a vuestro [__] rollo
We agree that windy
Estamos de acuerdo en que windy
disappeared from the internet
desapareció de internet
don't you all agree let's
no estáis todos de acuerdo a
see I'm looking at your lord grandfather But but
ver estoy mirando a tu señor abuelo Pero
well motorcycle but but well that
pero bueno motorcicle pero pero bueno
my wife is sleeping in my
que que está mi señora durmiendo en mi
piece of bed leave her alone
pedazo de cama déjala en paz
okay we all agree that
vale estamos todos de acuerdo en que
windy disappeared from the
windy desapareció de
Internet
Internet
But disappear
Pero desaparecer
disappear has disappeared serene where
desaparecer ha desaparecido serene dónde
the [ __ ] is serene Where is serene where the
[__] está
[ __ ] is
serene dónde [__] está
serene I  I'm cracking up at that [ __ ]
serene Yo es que me parto con esa [__]
[ __ ]. Hey, what a [ __ ] man,
payasada de [__] Eh qué payasada tío
historic [ __ ] that he and I are
payasada histórica que él y yo estamos
fine, I think that's what
bien que creo que eso es como lo lo que
should matter HM for Juanito I only
debe de importar HM para Juanito yo solo
have good words chat he truly
tengo buenas palabras chat él de verdad
is a wonderful person he is incredible
es una persona maravillosa es increíble
and I am very happy for all the years
y estoy muy contenta de todos los años
that he allowed me to know him, to be by his
que me permitió conocerlo de estar a su
side and well it will always continue to be like that I will
lado y y pues así va a seguir siendo
always be there for him he will always
siempre voy a estar para él siempre va a
have all my support and well we all
tener todo mi apoyo y bueno todos
know that Ari Gameplays has to
sabemos que Ari Gameplays tiene que
maintain her image as a diva streamer and that's why she
mantener su imagen de streamer diva y
can't go on camera all
por eso no puede salir a cámaras toda
disheveled and tearful to say I've
despeinada y llorosa a decir me he
divorced Juan and all that because it's not
divorciado de Juan y tal porque no es
part of her character that's why she hasn't
parte de su personaje por eso no lo ha
done it I think and you know the situation Or
hecho creo yo y sabes que la situación O
at least the relationship became so popular
al menos la relación se hizo tan popular
and so controversial that even the temach came out to give his
y tan polémica que hasta el temach salió
opinion and came out to support Juan
a opinar y salió a bancar a Juan
Guarnizo He went very very viral I mean I think it
guarnizo El fue muy muy viral o sea yo
's the tweet eh When I gave the
creo que es el tweet eh Cuando di la
exclusive I think it was the tweet that has
exclusiva creo que fue el tweet que más
had the most likes in my entire [ __ ] history
lik ha tenido en toda mi [__] historia
eh had the tweet
eh tuvo el tweet
120,000 like or something like that I don't remember maybe I'm
120.000 like o algo así no me acuerdo a
wrong save yourself [ __ ]
lo mejor me equivoco sálvate cabrón
save yourself [ __ ]
sálvate cabrón
save yourself possible divorce of Juan Guarnizo
sálvate sible divorcio de Juan guarnizo
and Ar and why do I say predictable because I had
y Ar y por qué digo predecible porque yo
already told you that this was going to happen
ya les había dicho que esto iba a pasar
all of us who have been on the channel for a while
todos los que llevamos un ratito en el
but this man Why does he say that
canal pero este hombre Por qué dice que
he already knew it was going to happen and that the
él ya sabía que iba a pasar y que el
fact that there is a divorce proves
hecho de que existe un divorcio le da a
him right about something dude you called
él la razón en algo se tío llamaste [__]
Ari a [ __ ] Simply because her husband
a Ari Simplemente porque el marido te
told you micropenis or so that's what
dijo micropene o sea eso es lo que
you did what the [ __ ] gives you right that
hiciste en qué [__] te da a ti la razón
yello got divorced I've never
que yello se divorci es que nunca he
understood this I've never
entendido esto de verdad nunca he
understood this man who comes out all
entendido este hombre que salga en plan
glorious like time proves me right Haha I
glorioso como el tiempo me da la razón
told you but he was saying that she was a
Jaja os lo dije pero estaba diciendo que
[ __ ] you weren't saying anything about them getting
era [__] tú no estabas diciendo nada de
divorced you guys ca
que se iban a divorciar a ustedes os ca
that this man said no no we all
que este hombre dijese no no todos
knew that they were getting divorced he didn't say it
sabíamos que se iban a divorciar no lo
life was messing with the woman
vida se estaban metiendo con la mujer
saying that she was a [ __ ] we knew that this  It was
diciendo que era [__] sabíamos que esto
going to happen and well, it undoubtedly
iba a pasar y pues bueno indudablemente
happened, they've been looking for me a lot, they've
pasó me han estado buscando mucho me han
been asking me my opinion on the
estado preguntando mi opinión al
matter and my opinion is the same as
respecto y mi opinión es la misma de
always, it's an opportunity for the guy who had his
siempre es una oportunidad para el vato
heart broken, it's an
que le rompieron el corazón es una
opportunity for the guy who's in the
oportunidad para el vato que está en el
hole, it's an opportunity for the person who is
hoyo es una oportunidad para la persona
realizing that he or she was not
que se está dando cuenta que no fue
valued, we don't know which of the
valorada o valorado no sabemos Cuál de
two is suffering more,
los dos está sufriendo más
eh, to go out, to get the Prime, to
eh Para salir para sacar el Prime para
improve, to connect, to have that
mejorar para conectar para tener ese
high, no further than the truth, I
subidón no más allá de la verdad yo
empathize with what the
empatizo con lo que ahorita le está
guy is going through right now, which is very different
pasando al compa que es muy diferente
from a year ago when we had our
que hace un año que tuvimos nuestras
differences. I just don't understand why,
diferencias Es que no entiendo por qué
eh, you encourage others to have their Prime when
eh anima a otros a tener su Prime cuando
you yourself don't have your Prime, the circumstance is not very
tú mismo No tienes tu Prime no es muy
different and it would be very
diferente la circunstancia y sería muy
incongruous on my part to make fun of
incongruente de mi parte burlarme de
someone who is suffering because of that
alguien que está sufriendo por eso
because all of us here, myself
porque todos los que estamos aquí yo
included, have been there, I said that
incluido hemos estado ahí eso lo decía
about everyone, anyone can tell, all
de todo el mundo así cualquiera acierta
watches, even the broken ones,
todos los relojes hasta los estropeados
tell the time right twice a day, no,
dan la hora bien dos veces al día no por
that's why we could have warned that this was
eso podríamos podíamos advertir que esto
going to happen, that's why we tried to
iba a pasar por eso lo Tratamos de
warn you  That's why we made fun of him because
advertir Por eso nos burlábamos porque
he didn't
él no se
realize what was going to happen and I've always
daba pas que iba a pasar y esto siempre
told them this when they say tem What do I do
se los he dicho cuando dicen tem Qué
with my friend who doesn't understand that no matter how
hago con mi compa que no entiende que
much I tell him he doesn't understand and he doesn't
por más que le digo no entiende y no se
realize because that's the problem with
da cuenta porque ese es el problema del
simpeo when you're inside you don't see it
simpeo cuando estás adentro no lo ves
wise words of temach And that I have
sabias palabras del temach Y eso que
never agreed with any red
nunca he estado de acuerdo con algún red
piller or some masculinity guru in
piller o algún gurú de masculinidad de
fact on this channel we have made fun
hecho en este canal ya hemos hecho mofa
of them several times and subscribe if you
de ellos varias veces y suscríbete si
want to see more of that anyway We never
quieres ver más de eso igual Nunca
knew what Juan
supimos Cómo era la relación de Juan
Guarnizo and Hari's relationship was like Gameplays from the inside
guarnizo y hari Gameplays desde adentro
how the two of them got along in their
como ellos dos se llevaban en su
marriage apparently they were doing quite
matrimonio ap entemente les iba bastante
well because they were even building
bien porque hasta se estaban haciendo
a house and now with the whole
una casa y ahora con todo el problema
divorce problem we don't know Whose house it will
del divorcio no sabemos De quién va a
be
ser la
continues or rather in reality I
casa continúa o sea en realidad yo me
imagine that what they will do is
imagino que esto lo que harán será
sell it or rather why are they going to stay
venderlo o sea para qué se van a quedar
right now none of them such a big
ahora mismo ninguno una casa tan grande
and familiar house a house that you were
y familiar una casa que te estabas
building with your ex-wife I mean I think they will
construyendo con tu ex mujer o sea yo
sell it I think it will be an investment
venderán yo creo que será una inversión
that they are going  to sell
que van a vender
[Music]
[Música]
But I honestly think they did the
Pero sinceramente creo que han hecho
right thing by getting divorced Juan Guarnizo
bien en divorciarse Juan guarnizo no
shouldn't have been in so much controversy
tenía que estar en tanta polémica por
because of his wife although he also
culpa de la esposa aunque él también se
earned his own problems no matter how
ganaba sus propios problemas por
stupid he was and the
estúpido que era y el proceso del
divorce process has been handled quite well
divorcio lo ha llevado bastante bien
Much better than we all expected
Mucho mejor de lo que todos esperábamos
because he even allows himself to make jokes
porque hasta se permite hacer bromas
about it with friends and friends are
sobre eso con los amigos y los amigos es
like Hey why are you doing that you just got
como que Oye por qué haces eso te acabas
divorced But at least you're
de divorciar Pero al menos ya lo estás
getting over it As long as you're happy everything's
superando Mientras esté feliz está todo
fine and after the announcement of his
bien y después del anuncio de su
divorce he took a couple of days
divorcio se tomó un par de días de
off and then he returned to normal
descanso y luego volvió con normalidad
always when one returns After
siempre cuando uno regresa Después de
several days of not streaming obviously but there's
varios días de no streamear obv pero est
a [ __ ] cameo I can't believe it
un [__] cameo no me lo puedo creer de
really I can't believe it man seriously no
verdad me no me lo puedo creer tío ya
jokes seriously can
fuera de coñas ya fuera de coñas
we totally watch a video one time where there's
totalmente podemos ver una vez un vídeo
no [ __ ]
en el que no haya un [__]
cameo I ask eh I ask I ask I
cameo pregunto eh pregunto pregunto
ask
pregunto pregunto
erase that watermark well no in
borren esa marca de agua pues no de
fact we're going to put the watermark
hecho la marca de agua la vamos a poner
in the middle all over your face because there are
en medio en toda la cara porque hay hay
a lot of people who live off my
un montón de gente que vive de mi cuenta
Twitter account and do like that and and  they cut the
de Twitter y hace así y y recortan el
video here and there you know and it's like
vídeo por aquí y por acá sabes y es como
dude like but let's go a bunch of people
tío o sea pero vamos un montón de Peña
eh who upload a lot of you know look at the
eh que sube un montón de sabes a ver la
Twitter account of pum the gossip
cuenta de Twitter de pum el del salseo
no no but it's that there's always not a [ __ ]
no no pero es que siempre no hay un [__]
video that we see that didn't come from
vídeo que veamos que no ha salo de
us Eh yeah the fame is already there
nosotros Eh sí ya está la [__] de la
the truth is I'm going to retire at
fama la verdad me voy a retirar en
any moment I'm also a little
cualquier momento tambén hay un poquito
nervous And look I've been doing this for 8 years
de nervio Y mira que llevo 8 años
and maybe the existence of
haciéndolo y tal vez la existencia de
Javi Oliveira is very necessary on the
Javi oliveira es muy necesaria en
internet totally I agree I
internet totalmente estoy de acuerdo
agree if you want the
estoy de acuerdo si queréis que siga la
existence to continue we're going to reach 4000
existencia vamos a llegar a 4000
members tonight not so much what do you
miembros esta noche no tanto que os
care about my existence no [ __ ] I mean it's gone
importa mi existencia no hijos de [__] o
the party's gone the
sea se ha apagado se apagó la fiesta no
party's not gone no What's going on How many We've
se apagó la fiesta no Qué pasa Cuántos
reached
Hemos llegado
eh 169 members That's all that's all
eh 169 miembros Eso es todo eso es todo
kids
chavalería
and I still haven't gotten a member says Gael
y sigue sin caerme un miembro dice Gael
gift son of a
regalo hijo
[ __ ] lauti has given away
[__] lauti ha regalado
100 lauti has given away
100 lauti ha regalado
100 here 2005 people you can't give away
100 aquí 2005 personas no podéis regalar
100 mrec
100 mrec cada
each no no Elia no no no no loelia the
uno no no Elia no no no no loelia la
truth is you can't give away 100 thousand
verdad no podéis regalar 100 mi illos
each what? It's 100 quinces to
cada uno queé Son 100 membrillos a
one but but I'm freaking out with the people this
uno pero peroo flipo con la peña esta
time for x or y reasons Maybe
ocasión por x Oy razones A lo mejor
your grandpa will give one away let's see It's that
regala uno tú abuelo a ver Es que la
move that
movida que se
some creators supposedly had put in place
supone que habían puesto algunos
so they can give away
creadores para que puedan regalar
members But they haven't put it
miembros Pero a mí no me la han puesto
on any of the channels man, I mean I
en ninguno de los canales tío o sea lo
'm seeing it down here and I can't
estoy viendo por aquí abajo y a mí no me
give away members it's like a
sale para regalar miembro es como una
free amount of members for
cantidad de miembros gratu para para los
followers and whoever it touches no but they have
seguidores y a quien le toque no pero a
n't put it on me I don't know why
mí no me la han puesto no sé por qué
eh There are things that make it more tense than
eh Hay cosas que lo hacen más tenso de
normal I'm not saying I'm talking about those
lo normal no digo yo hablando de ese
types of comments I realized one
tipo de comentarios me di cuenta de una
thing these days that I was away how
cosa estos días que estuve fuera lo
much it bothers my friends when I
mucho que le incomoda a mis amigos que
make funny comments about the subject but
haga comentarios graciosos del tema pero
incredible eh I've found passion in making them
increíble eh he encontrado pasión en
uncomfortable and what I like the most is
incomodarlos y lo que más me gusta es
that they still see it As soon as
que ellos aún lo ven Tan pronto como
to get on par you know well at this
para ponerse a la par sabes pues en este
moment I'm the only one who can
momento yo soy el único que puede
do it  we were in a restaurant
hacerlo estábamos en un restaurante
first day when we arrived and the waiter
primer día al llegar y el meser nos
asked us how are you guys everything ok
pregunta cómo Cómo están Todo bien
I told them I'm not going through a
chicos les dije no estoy pasando por un
divorce nobody laughed the only one who
divorcio nadie se rió el único que se
laughed was me and in the end the secret maybe
rió fui yo y al final el secreto quizás
wasn't leaving Ari Gameplays Maybe the
no era dejar a Ari Gameplays Quizás lo
only thing Juan Guarnizo needed to
único que necesitaba Juan guarnizo para
be happy was to have a beard and stop
ser feliz era tener una barba y dejar de
having that cuc face he had because ever
tener esa cara de cuc que tenía porque
since he grew a beard he
desde que se dejó la barba
automatically started to seem more
automáticamente empezó a parecerle más
attractive to the women on Twitter Juan
atractivo a las mujeres de Twitter Juan
Guarnizo turn me on please You don't
guarnizo prendame por favor No
know how to see ugly it's never been Apart from
sabes a ver feo no ha sido nunca Aparte
this beard is a little ugly it would have to be
esta Barba es un poco fea se la tendría
fixed it's like a beard that you have
que arreglar es como una barba de que
n't shaved for two weeks because you
lleva dos semanas sin afeitarte porque
don't have
no tienes
time it remains to be explored your body I
tiempo quedaría por recorer tu cuerpo me
love you too much since you're
encantas demasiado desde que andas
single you look very good my God how
soltero te ves muy bien Dios mío qué
delicious Hey mencha but mencha really what do
rico Oye mencha pero mencha de verdad
you have against me I mean mencha is a
que tienes en contra o sea mencha es una
lady I understand that I don't know if she's from the
señora entiendo que no sé si es de la
lordship because of course mencha has been in
señoría porque claro mencha ha estado en
the telesalseo chat trying to get
el chat de telesalseo intentando que la
people not to give away members don't cry anymore
gente no regalase miembro no llores más
Javi you're like Jeremiah and she came
Javi eres como Jeremías y se ha venido
here here he has seen that you have
aquí aquí ha visto que que me habéis
given me 170 members and he is trying to
regalado 170 miembros y está intentando
convince you that I did not give away members
convenceros de que no regalé miembros
here either men chuca What problem do
aquí tampoco men chuca Qué problema
you have
tienes por
why which is your What's the
qué cuál es tu Cuál es la
thing What's the thing Hey sabot is
vaina Cuál es la vaina Oye sabot te está
sabotaging you no no but completely but the
saboteando no no pero completamente pero
worst thing is that it is taking
es que lo peor es que está haciendo
effect because he said so and
efecto porque lo ha dicho y
automatically there are no more members
automáticamente ya no hay miembros
Oh I already woke up good dog morning and the
Oh ya me levanté buenos perros días y la
conclusion of today's video is Grow a
conclusión del video de hoy es Déjate la
beard to be more handsome and if you don't
barba para que seas más guapo y si no la
have one then already F Well that was all bye well
tienes pues ya F Bueno solo era eso chao
Totally agree the truth is
pues Totalmente de acuerdo la verdad
let's go see a bit of Frank let's go see
vamos a ver un poco a Frank vamos a ver
a bit of Fran sis
un poco a Fran sis
Ah Totally agree
Ah Totalmente de acuerdo
francoa let's see let's see two videos two
francoa a ver a ver dos vídeos dos
videos let's try to have
vídeos vamos a intentar que nos dé
time for both of us while Andy is
tiempo a los dos mientras que Andy está
making the miniature let's try to
haciendo la miniatura vamos a intentar
have time for both of us okay let's see
que nos dé tiempo a los dos vale de ver
both videos I want to see how they
los dos vídeos Quiero ver a ver cómo se
adapt to the
adaptan al
medium and me Juan because come on plex has
medio y yo Juan porque vamos plex ha ido
already gone to the sanctuary of the son of a [ __ ] eh Well I don't even
ya al santuario del hijo [__] eh Pues no
know how many times that one has fallen no that one doesn't
sé ya ni las veces caído ese no ese no
even keep count that one  go go to the
lleva ni la cuenta ese va va al
sanctuary like me to Mercadona well no [ __ ]
santuario como yo al mercadona bueno no
I only go to Mercadona at
[__] yo al mercadona nada más que voy a
7 in the afternoon to see if I get laid so
las 7 de la tarde para ver si ligo pues
guys eh the plan is for Jo Juan to have a
chicos eh el plan es que Jo Juan lo pase
bad time but this one has a bad time
mal pero que lo pase mal este qui A ver
Let's see what the crazy guy wants push him thrust
vamos a ver qué quiere el loco empújale
him ha two days ago we were in
empale ha hace dos días estábamos en
Japan with a jet up our ass in a
Japón con un chorro metido por el culo
Última Generación toilet and now we
en water de Última Generación y ahora
're here push him Give him a little
estamos aquí empújale Dale un
push give him a little push give him a little push
empujoncito dale un empujoncito dale un
What are you doing dude You
empujoncito Qué haces cabrón Tú
[ __ ] are they canceling Juan because of
[__] están cancelando ellos Juan por
this let's see also I'll tell you one thing eh
esto a ver también te digo una cosa eh
eh watch out how crazy the kids are eh
eh ojo que loco es de la chavalería eh
in my kangaroo let's see I have to admit
en mi canguro a ver tengo que reconocer
that it didn't sit well with me eh It didn't
que no me ha sentado bien eh No me ha
sit well with me Let's see it's evidently I
sentado bien A ver es que evidentemente
don't think people are going a
no creo que la gente se está pasando un
bit too far they're saying animal abuse I don't know
poco está diciendo maltrato animal no sé
how much It's not a problem if you push the
sé cuánto No pasa nada porque empujes al
kangaroo but it's true it seems like he did
canguro pero sí que es verdad como que
n't measure much force I mean he's a he's a Let's
no ha medido mucho la la fuerza o sea es
see he's not a well he's a
un es una A ver no es una bueno es
teenager  it's a baby it's not a it's not
adolescente es una cría no es un no es
an adult I mean no it's not going to do
un adulto O sea no te no te va a hacer
anything to you the
nada el
kangaroo can give you a scare it
canguro te puede dar un susto que te
asks you by surprise which I understand is what
pide de sorpresa que entiendo que es lo
happened to it not that it caught it by
que le ha pasado no que le ha pillado de
surprise and all But damn [ __ ] There's no
sorpresa Y tal Pero [__] [__] No hace
need to hit it you know it hasn't
falta que le pegue sabes que no ha
measured its strength I mean it's a little kangaroo
medido la fuerza o sea es un cangurito
I understand that if it were a that yes if it
entiendo que si fuera un que si que si
were an adult an adult kangaroo then
fuera un adulto un canguro adulto pues
you get scared because it grabs you And then you
te asustes porque te agarra Y entonces
use all your strength to push it
utilices todas tu fuerza para empujarlo
but right now it feels
para tal pero ahora mismo me ha sentado
bad the truth no no to me let's see
mal la verdad no no a mí a ver
obviously I understand that it was that it was a
evidentemente entiendo que ha sido que
mistake no I mean it was
que se ha equivocado no O sea que ha
like it was by accident that it got scared And it
como sin querer que se ha asustado Y ha
reacted like that you know not being
reaccionado así sabes no estar
used to being with kangaroos and
acostumbrado a a a estar con canguros y
we were already like that and me Juan vs the grandfather
nosotros ya así y yo Juan vs el abuelo
at the evening to defend the honor of
en la velada para defender el honor de
crazy defend your kangaroo xurra Well I don't
loco defiende a tu canguro xurra Pues no
know I don't know but I think Yan is
lo sé No lo sé pero creo que yan está
strong eh I mean I don't know what he will be like in
fuerte eh o sea no sé cómo será en
person but I think he is strong eh I
persona pero creo que está fuerte eh o
mean he looks strong come on  a little
sea se ve fuertote dale un
bit What are you doing, [ __ ]? Realize that the
pocito Qué haces cabrón date cuenta que
plex is tall, he's a
el el plex es alto tela le saca una
head taller than Frank and Fran is a head taller
cabeza a Frank y Fran me saca una cabeza
than
a
me. All the [ __ ], I push him
mí todo [__] lo empujo
too much. Hey, he's an athlete, he's an athlete, he's an
demasiado Oye es un atleta eh es un
athlete. You're really
atleta eh es un atleta [__] estás
strong, [ __ ]. What the [ __ ] is an
fuerte cabrón pero qué [__] es un
athlete? I felt dangerous when I was
atleta eh Me he sentío un peligro
defended, but hey, but but, this this. How did he
defendido pero Oye pero per pero este
jump? How did he jump?
este Cómo ha saltado Cómo ha saltado
These people have resentment, but behind the
tienen rencor esta gente pes detrás de
clock, no, just in case, I do. Put it here.
la hora no por si acaso yo sí Pon Aquí
These people have resentment, they are resentful.
tienen rencor esta gente son rencorosos
Yes. Come closer, man. He'll hit you three
sí Acércate hombre te pega tres te pega
times. He'll kick you four times. Now they forgive me, but no. Forget
cuatro patadas ahora perdonan pero no
me. Of course, of course, now he'll kick you
Olvídame Claro claro ahora te pega
four times. You don't know what this is. Okay,
cuatro patadas no sabes lo que es
very
vale muy
slowly, I haven't seen this, man, I
despacio yo esto no lo he visto tío lo
saw it today in a Twitter clip, but
he visto hoy en un clip de Twitter pero
I haven't seen this in the sanctuary. I do
yo esto no lo he visto en el santuario
n't even know where the [ __ ] it is. Happen
esto no sé ni dónde [__] está pasar
with me, right? I haven't seen this. I
conmigo cl que esto no lo he visto esto
don't even know where the [ __ ] this is. The idea is
no sé ni dónde [__] está esto la idea
Juan.
Juan
Look, the idea is Juan. It
Mira la idea Juan
's to cut. Look, listen to how he
es cortar Mira escucha como
breathes. You get sauce from where there isn't any. No,
respira sacáis salseo de donde no hay no
no, yes, we're not getting it.  I'm saying that if
no si no estamos sacando salseo si es
people were making fun of him Alo Juan
que la gente lo estaba funando Alo Juan
that's why it doesn't seem like a joke to me
por eso a mí no me parece para funar Lo
eh he lost his strength obviously he
eh se le ha ido la fuerza evidentemente
pushed him too hard but I
le ha empujado demasiado fuerte pero
understand that it was a reaction eh in the
entiendo que ha sido una reacción eh al
end it's a wild animal that's
final es un animal salvaje que te está
attacking you and no you don't think [ __ ] well it
atacando y no tú no piensas [__] pues
's a puppy or I don't know what you
es un cachorro o no sé qué tú has
reacted because you think it's going to do
reacionado porque te crees que te va hac
something to you you know what I mean I don't know the truth I don't know
algo me entiendes No sé la verdad no sé
the truth either it's not worth making fun of it it's not
la verdad tampoco es para funar lo no es
obviously
evidentemente
[ __ ] have you
ostia has
heard God they look like the waves of the sea
escuchado Dios parecen las olas del mar
well well the waves of the sea the
bueno bueno las olas del mar el
romantic as hell but listen
romántico de los [__] pero escucha
like listen how do you do
como escucha comoo hac
eh father asleep okay my father seems
eh padre dormo vale parece mi padre
asleep say Juan is that we are going to come and we are
dormido di Juan es que vamos a venir y
going to cut this piece that piece
vamos a cortar este trozo ese trozo lo
we are going to cut it well because it has been has been
vamos a cortar bien porque ha estado ha
very is very
estado muy está muy
[ __ ] this is a dead piece okay if
[__] esto es un trozo muerto ya vale si
you notice this is a dead piece you
te das cuenta esto es un trozo muerto lo
see And this is a live piece you see the
ves Y esto es un trozo vivo ves la
difference in color So we are going to
diferencia de color Entonces vamos a
cut this part where the bees
cortar esta parte donde ya las abejas no
are no longer okay And we can't eat that
están vale Y eso no lo podemos comer
and this not when we cut it what goes  to
nosotros y esto no al cortarlo lo que va
do is that honey is going to fall Here we are going to
a hacer es que va a caer miel Aquí vamos
put a bucket and honey is going to fall okay And we are
a poner un cubo y va a caer miel vale Y
going to eat that honey okay Of course
esa miel la vamos a comer vale Claro
but when I cut it aren't they going to get mad
pero cuando lo corte no se van a enfadar
at us not quite quite right
con nosotros no bastante bastante verdad
okay How exciting how appetizing besides here it's
vale Qué ganas qu apetecible además aquí
very recently
hace muy poco
hot in Malaga
calores de Málaga
man it's hot J it's so hot that I've
[__] hace calor J ha mucho calor que
never hab that I've never
nunca hab que nunca
hab that you've never been so close to a
hab que no habías estado tan cerca de un
bee canal this big then of
canal de abejas este grande entonces
course I've been watching it these days
claro yo lo estado observando estos días
and you see all this part there are bees around
y ves toda esta parte hay abejas por
here behind but this is dead you see it
aquí detrás pero esto está muerto lo ves
can be cut easily a lot Fran there's no
se puede cortar fáil mucho Fran no hace
need to lie to it's not necessary we
falta que men to que no hace falta
'll have to go buy something to
tendremos que ir a comprar algo para
protect don't touch Fran don't touch don't touch it's
proteger no toque Fran no toque no toque
not necessary eh To protect yourselves that we
que no hace falta eh Para protegeros que
get into plan they are going to attack us they are going
nos ponemos en plan nos van a atacar nos
to of course we are not going to come in
van a claro no vamos a venir en
croc a kiss
croc un beso
Yoli we are going to buy some
Yoli vamos a comprar una protección
professional protection exactly
profesional exacto
the good ones of the good ones of the
de la buena de la tocha de la buena de
whole life that are used stings you
toda la vida que se utiliza picotazos te
die no no you're not going to die But come on
mueres no no te vas a morir Pero vamos
you can fall some that they are going to
que te puedes caer unos que nos van a
sting us for sure besides These are the
caer picotazo seguro además Estas son
fighters eh these are called the
las peleonas eh estas les llam las
fighters here the Fighter Look how it is
peleonas aquí las Fighter Mira cómo está
Look how it is
Mira cómo
in a moment they come out to attack you can
está en un momento salen a atacar se les
hear them Eh yes they are ready to attack they
escucha Eh sí ya están para atacar ya
are ready to attack Come on this here will be
están para atacar Hala esto de aquí será
[ __ ] you scare eh you put that on
cabrón te da miedo eh eso lo has puesto
purpose [ __ ] what do you think I
tu aposta [__] qu te crees que he
hung one and he died there with
colgado a uno y se me ha muerto ahí con
music guys we are getting dressed
música chavales estamos cogiendo ropa
because we are going to kill me Juan
porque vamos a matar a yo Juan
indeed we have to protect ourselves
efectivamente hay que protegerse
strongly he is already used to these
fuerte ya está acostumbrado a estas
things I have already learned my lesson from everything
cosas Yo ya estoy escarmentado de todo
but we are going to raise one that you are going to
pero vamos a montar una que os vais a
[ __ ] yourselves I mean I am not saying what we are going to do
[__] O sea no digo lo que vamos a hacer
But we are getting dressed to protect ourselves it is going to be
Pero estamos cogiendo ropa para
some move It could be
protegernos va a ser una movida Puede
robbing a bank or now you will see
que sea robar un banco o ahora lo veréis
or charge this or charge It is that he is
o cargarnos a esto o cargar Es que es
a son of a [ __ ] guy is It is that
que er un hijo de [__] tío es Es que
Enjoy this guy he likes it Look look look look look
Disfruta este tío le gusta tío Mira mira
how he does pay
mira mira mira cómo
attention guys what is coming eh it is
hace atentos chavales que se viene eh se
coming
viene
hot well they are getting dressed because what we are
gorda bueno se están vistiendo porque lo
going to do is
que vamos a hacer es hacer una
collect honey today Dinner guys
recolección de miel hoy Se cena chavales
today Dinner feral
hoy Se cena ferale
and the  Thais are boys not Fran
y los tailandeses son chicos no Fran
because this is about two planes like
porque esto es unas dos planos como de
Sab has a plane FR the callas are very noticeable
sab ha un plano FR las callas se nota
in the sizes it is noticeable What a madness man I
en las tallas se nota Qué locura tío
take This I take this What a madness that
levo Esto me llevo esto Qué locura que
we are doing this
estemos haciendo esto
man its wonderful Oh look there is
tío una maravilla Ay mira está ah el
Ricky and I want her what I don't want are
Ricky y la quiero lo que no quiero son
pecks on the face that already
picotazos en la cara que ya la semana
last week you some pecks that didn't They
pasada ti unos picotazos que no Me
looked for
buscaron
anything on me lacha south
nada lacha sud se
the chest of suda is coming
viene la pechada de suda que se viene
this is coming really
esto viene bien
down it has gotten est I don't know look
abajo se ha metido est yo no sé mira
the otters are there I don't know where the
están las nutrias ahí yo no sé dónde
[ __ ] this thing of the aej is in the
[__] está esto de las aej en el
sanctuary I have no [ __ ] idea
santuario no tengo ni putísima idea
Where is this the truth is I don't
Dónde está esto la verdad ni es que no
even know where it can be let's
se me ocurre ni siquiera por dónde puede
see with what serene it went to
estar a ver con qué serene fue a parar
where Fran you can already see that the
allá donde Fran ya se le vea que las
bees leia F for serene a kiss guys we
abejas leia F por serene un beso chicos
already have a thumbnail for the video of the
ya tenemos miniatura para el vídeo del
Main Channel from here we are going to
Canal principal de aquí nos vamos a
make an r for the main channel
hacer una r para el canal principal
when we see This video Now we go
cuando veamos Este vídeo Ahora nos vamos
to the premiere of the Main Channel that we
al estreno del Canal principal que
have to support the video really hard
tenemos que apoyar bien fuerte el vídeo
Damn What is going to come out  a little late it's
[__] Que que va a salir un poquito tarde
going to be a little late today for the
que va a salir un poquillo tarde hoy el
video let's see guys one important thing
vídeo a ver chicos una cosa importante
first when we enter don't make noise don't
primero cuando entramos no hagáis ruido
make it Don't talk too much no where the [ __ ] heo it
no hagáis No habléis mucho no dónde [__]
looks worse because he trips on the
heo se ve peor porque se tropieza con la
tire mu
llanta mu
tire low okay very low the most
llanta baj vale muy bajito lo más
important thing is not to panic right
importante no hay que paniquear verdad
Fran is there
Fran ya está
no Juan is keeping the house and did a
no Juan se queda con la casa e hizo un
House tour but he will sell it surely he is
House tour pero la venderá seguramente
not going to keep that
no se va a quedar con esa casa tan
big house I have it on my right right
grande la tengo a mi derecha verdad
plex
plex
calories you take out you take out especially wax and
caloras sacas sacas sobre todo cera y
such this he takes it Ugh what a chunk and he's taking out
tal esto lo coge Uf qué tocho y va
a little bit of he's taking out a
sacando un poquito de va sacando un
little bit of honey there are
poquito de miel hay
parts Look This is okay this is dead you
partes Mira Esto vale esto está muerto
see all this that is dead Look at it do
ves todo esto que está muerto Mira est
n't pick it up Don't pick it up Don't
no la levantes No la levantes No lo
pick it up
levantes
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
eh
eh se
all this is over it's dead
acabó todo esto que está muerto
let's see let's see the other one today
veis a ver vamos a ver el otro el de hoy
plex eo Juan attacked in the sanctuary it's that they
plex eo Juan atacados en el santuario es
have uploaded like a click that me
que han subido como un click de que yo
Juan and plex are
Juan y plex están
hospitalized because he has been attacked by
hospitalizados porque le ha atacado
some crazy animal What has it done What has
algún animal loco Qué ha hecho Qué ha
done what's happened to
hecho qué ha pasado
you what's happened to you Look my
contigo qué ha pasado contigo Mira mi
crazy one is still the same I have to go because
loco sigue igual tengo que ir porque
Play is taking the youtubers to the
Play está llevando a los youtubers al
sanctuary Yes we all know that Fran doesn't
santuario Si todos sabemos que a Fran no
like visits to see
le gustan las visitas a ver
eh No It's not that he doesn't like
eh No a No es que no le gusten las
visits well not that he loves them
visitas bueno tampoco que le encanten
but above all it's the animals that he does
pero sobre todo es a los animales a los
n't really like having people around
que no le gusta mucho tener gente por
there to see plex is from the house so
allí a ver plex es de la casa entonces
if he goes with a friend he can do it and that's it I mean it's
si va con un amigo puede hacerlo y punto
not a big deal eh it's for one day I mean I think that I think
o sea tampoco pasa nada eh es un día o
with shokas I
sea yo creo que yo creo que con shokas
think he was there for one day a day or a day and a
creo que estuvo un día un día o día y
half I mean I don't think they even stayed there to
medio o sea creo que no se quedaron allí
sleep And in this case I think
a dormir siquiera Y en este caso creo
that
que yo
Juan too I mean they've been there and
Juan igual o sea han pasado por ahí y
outside you have to go and spend Christmas there
fuera tienes que ir y pasar Navidad allí
at Christmas I'm going to take a vacation
en Navidad voy a a hacer unas vacaciones
with friends or with friends with
con los amigos u con los amigos con la
family
familia
but but
pero
the problem I have with
pero es que el problema que tengo con el
going to the sanctuary is that I leave
tema de ir al santuario Es que yo dejo
Lorena here then she's alone you know with
aquí a Lorena entonces sola sabes con
everything with everything with the house the children and
todo con toda con la casa los niños y
right now Lorena is studying in
ahora mismo Lorena está estudiando por
the mornings she has the same thing as
las mañanas tien la misma de esto que
the children at school So I
los niños del colegio Entonces yo no
can't  right now let's go let's go let's
puedo ahora mismo des aviar la vamos des
go no, the house belongs to
aviar la des aviar no que la casa es de
both of us and the children are both of us
los dos y los niños son de los dos
obviously it's both of our jobs it's
evidentemente es trabajo de los dos es
both of our responsibilities and when she
responsabilidad de los dos y cuando ella
's on vacation Well, I don't know if I'm going to be
esté de vacaciones Pues no sé si voy a
able to miss a few days to go to the
poder perder unos días para ir al
sanctuary you know instead of I don't know the
santuario sabes en vez de no sé la
truth It depends depends at the moment
verdad Depende depende de momento
we have some vacation organized as a
tenemos unas vacaciones organizadas en
family so I don't know when maybe
familia entonces no sé cuándo tal vez
for next year like
para el año que viene en plan semana
Easter or something like that maybe I don't know
santa o algo de eso a lo mejor no lo sé
but man I want to go I
pero hombre tengo ganas de ir tengo
want to go to the sanctuary soon yes I
ganas de ir pronto al santuario sí tengo
want to go soon no no you're going to see me
ganas de ir pronto no no me vais a ver
there in the very distant future it's not going to be
ahí en un futuro muy lejano no va a ser
very
muy
far what happened where have you been
lejano qué ha pasado dónde te has metido
what the hell have you done
qué [__] ha hecho
man Where have you been apart I want I
tío Dónde te habrás metido aparte Quiero
want to go before he
quiero ir antes de que loco
grows up crazy you got caught in the storm
crezca te ha pillado la tormenta
eh guys today what we did was
eh chicos hoy lo que hemos hecho es
clean the otters' mess come
limpiar el el cacharro de las nutrias
come what mess ah the pool
venir venir qué cacharro ah la piscinita
Come on Juan We have Juan here who you
Hala Juan Tenemos aquí a Juan que lo
know as illo Juan okay he
conocéis por illo Juan vale que ha
came to Thailand what  let's [ __ ] him
venido a Tailandia que le demos por el
up and [ __ ] him up eh No Not really
culo y le jodamos eh No En realidad no
but it's your intention no now I ca
pero es tu intención no ahora yo puedo
n't let myself know let's kill I'm going to
no dejarme sab vamos a matar yo te voy a
tell you that his face changes as
decir que su cara va cambiando según le
you tell him things I see him more and more
vas diciendo cosas cada vez le veo más
now I introduce him because ah I don't even
ahora lo presento porque a es que ni lo
introduce him but come on it's like he was
presento pero vamos es que como si fuera
the otter the plex right okay look look look look look look we
ya la nutria el plex verdad vale mira
put
metido
little fish in them Why will you say how bad you are
pececitos Por qué diréis qué malo eres
why do you put fish damn Well because they
por qué metes peces [__] Pues porque
are otters
porque son nutrias
[ __ ] and those PC and those
[__] y esos PC y esos
PC what has he put fish Why has he put
PC qué ha metido pes Por qué ha metido
fish how difficult
pes
eh what they do they confuse them so they
eh lo que hacen ellas los confunden para
don't go in a
que no vayan en
group Then they take them out until
grupo Entonces los van sacando hasta que
one is left loose one is left loose they
queda uno suelto queda uno suelto los
corner them I didn't know it's brutally funny
acorralan no sabía es brutal gracioso
laqu no I didn't know I didn't
laqu no no sabía no
know stimulate his different animal How
sabía estimular su distinto animal Qué
funny
gracioso
eh the animals dude uuuuu and have you seen
eh los animales tío uuuuu y habéis visto
the movie El Fútbol this dude is
la película de El Fútbol esto tío es
like soccer no no in the end they catch it it's
como el fútbol no no al final pillan es
like Ping Pong you know it goes looking like this
como el Pimpón sabes va viendo así
left right left right the
izquierda derecha izquierda derecha la
host Look look look look look look  look look he has it he has it
[__] Mira mira mira mira mir mir mira
no yes he has it he has it he has it he has it
mira la tiene la tiene no sí lo tiene lo
yes he caught it
tiene lo tiene lo tiene sí la ha pillado
No no yes yes yes yes yes he has already swallowed it damn
No no sí sí sí sí sí ya se la ha tragado
well he has it he has it he has it he has it he is done he has it Look look look look
[__] pues lo tiene lo tiene lo tiene
what he's doing He's playing with it
mira mira qué hace Está jugando con él
playing but they don't kill it yes he eats it already
jugar pero no lo matan sí se lo come ya
left touched Yeah there it is the fish he
lo dejado tocadito Sí ya está el pez lo
has it already stunned he has it stunned and he's
tiene ya atontado lo tiene atontado y va
playing with it look look look how he
jugando con él mira mira mira cómo lo
has it between his legs and now it will come out
tiene entre las patas y ahora saldrá
now it will come out with it and eat it
ahora va a salir con él y se lo come
outside you
fuera
see it comes out with it and eats it outside or
ves sale con él y se lo come fuera o ahí
right there look the otters play with their
mismo mira las nutrias juegan con su
food What they say kids don't play
comida Eso que dicen niños no juegues
with food well otters do play
con la comida pues las nutrias si juegan
with
con la
food damn they do play with food
comida [__] sí juegan con la comida
always they always do it they don't eat normally
siempre siempre lo hacen no comen normal
no he's a little psychopathic it's like
no es un poco psicópata es como que
the scorpions are very mean like gallows
lasas son muy cabronas como las horcas
no gallows don't do something like that either
no las horcas no hacen algo así también
the seals have fun killing it's like he
las focas divierte matar es como que
enjoys seeing how it is already weak like he
disfruta viendo como ya está débil como
knows that it is not going to escape
que sabe que ya no se le va a escapar
look and the fish is pitiful now it swims very
mira y el pez da penilla ya como nada
slowly  He keeps pounding away at it until he
lentísimo lo va machacando hasta que ya
finally says, well, how do you see this one, she does
al final dice pues me lo como ves
n't get it, no,
est no pilla no más
younger, but you see when she catches that one, when
joven pero ves cuando pille esa cuando
Dalsi catches them, she'll eat it right away, that's the
dals pille se lo come al momento es la
difference with Plexi, Plexi is playing
diferencia con plexi plexi está jugando
and you see that they respect each other, the
y ves que se respetan no viene a por él
other one doesn't come for him, the other one doesn't come for this one
la otra la otra no viene a por este
because this one is already hers, there's a
porque este ya es de ella ent ahí hay un
respect that later maybe she'll even get it
respeto que luego a lo mejor hasta se lo
when Plexi doesn't want it anymore,
coge cuando ya plexi no lo quiera
a fish gets tired of swimming, eh, yeah, man, of
un pez se cansa de nadar eh s hombre
course, yeah, like, like, he gets
claro Sí en
tired like a human of
plan en plan se cansa como un humano de
cardio or no, yes, he gets tired, he gets tired of
cardio o no sí se cansa se cansa de
cardio, what you're planning is imagine a fish
cardio tú es que plan me imagina un pez
trains in the
entrena en el
altaf, what you're saying is true, no, they don't
altaf es verdad lo que dices que no no
interfere, each one is doing their
interfieren cada uno cada uno está lo
own thing, look, look, I'll get it now. Look, it's
suyo mira mira ya lo Pillo Mira ves es
what I told you, when I catch him,
lo que te dije cuando lo coja
Dalsi is playing but he's going to get bitten, they're already
dalsi juega pero le va a enganchar un
playing. Look, yeah, but
mordisco están Ya jugando Mira s Pero
look, his mouth is already there. Look, it's done, now
mira ya se la boca Mira ya está ahora
you're eating. No, no, he's still playing and
comes No todavía no todavía juega y
in a while we'll see them
dentro de un rato las veremos en esta
tonight, they've all eaten it, let's see.  yes let's
noche se lo han comido todos s a ver si
see if I can recognize it
la a ver si la soy capaz de reconocer
Javi you have stepped on small land
Javi has pisado campo poco campo
too much urban land why did I give it no no
demasiado urbanita por qué lo di no no
but totally entity But why do you
pero total ente Pero por qué lo
say that and with this they have enough for the whole day
dices y con esto tienen para todo el día
with this they have enough for a while for
con esto tienen para para un rato para
a while only this they eat snails
un rato solo esto se comen caracoles
worms crickets fish
gusanos Grillos peces
rats he came today he came Ho and
ratas ha venido él hoy ha venido Ho y
when this crazy guy gets going you
cuando se pone este chalado ha lo
push him and you have to push eating
empujas y loenes que empujar comiendo
there the fish and the seals Look look look they
ahí los peces y las focas Mira mira mira
are already eating look look
ya están comiendo mira
that is dalsy if I'm not mistaken This
mira esa es dalsy si no me equivoco Esta
is dalsy she is the one with the
es dalsy es la que tiene la cabeza
different head V has played a little and
diferente V se ha jugado un poquito y
now she has it yes it is dalsy very plexi
ahora ya lo tiene sí es dalsy bien plexi
Ah well no [ __ ] well I don't have to go
Ah pues no [__] pues no tengo que ir
eh I don't recognize her or my otters she
eh Ya no la reconozco ni a mis nutrias
ate the whole thing [ __ ] plexi is my
se la comido entero [__] plexi es mi
WhatsApp profile picture in fact for
foto de perfil del WhatsApp de hecho por
another head Ah he only eats the head
otro la cabeza Ah solo se come la cabeza
because plexi is like rounder the
es que plexi es como más redondita la
head Lu
cabeza Lu se lo
eats it imagine the role of the fish
come imagínate el papel de los peces
now swimming over there and seeing the
ahora nadando para allá y viendo el
corpse of the colleague  yours floating is not
cadáver del colega suyo flotando no es
that I was seeing on WhatsApp that I
que estaba viendo en WhatsApp que me
was laughing my ass off because they
estaba descojonando porque me han
sent me this
mandado esta
screenshot They sent me this screenshot and it's
captura Me han mandado esta captura y es
like of course daughter you can't wait How
como claro hija no puedes agu Qué
difficult it is for me to keep quiet these two
difícil me pone el callarme estos dos
idiots no no shutting up
estúpido no no el callarte no te lo
we don't make it difficult for you Peppa It's that I
ponemos nosotros difícil Peppa Es que
was with 100 viewers not even
estabajo hoy con 100 espectadores ni ni
48 hours are you going to put up with doing a
48 horas vas vas a aguantar en hacer un
live about Javi Because you're my
directo sobre Javi Porque eres mi
stalker
acosadora
my stalker no no this morning they uploaded
mi acosadora no no esta mañana subieron
a screenshot that the live stream is
una captura de que el los directos está
having 100 viewers what it says
teniendo 100 espectadores ya lo que pone
here that we have talked about
aquí que nosotros hemos hablado de
Amparo I don't
Amparo No
know no How difficult How difficult it is for me to
sé no Qué difícil Qué difícil se me pone
shut up No no it's that you're not going to shut up
callarme No no es que no te vas a callar
pppa it's that you're not going to shut up it's that you
pppa es que no te vas a callar es que tú
're my
eres mi
stalker at the moment what are you doing
acosadora de momento que qu haces
commenting on a
comentando un
tit But it wasn't even with her Of course it's
tet Pero si ni era con ella el Claro que
not about her but it's that she had
no va con ella pero es que ella tenía
100 viewers at the time she
100 espectadores en el momento que ha
said she wasn't going to talk about me and she's not going
dicho que no iba a hablar de mí y no va
to stop she's never going to stop until I
a parar no va a parar nunca hasta que no
stop her  the law is not going to stop without a head
la pare la ley no va a parar sin cabeza
Look Pedrito what a nightmare eh [ __ ] it
Mira Pedrito vaya pesadilla eh [__]
has only eaten his head yes he says it
solo le ha comido la cabeza sí dice que
is the tastiest Look at this Look at
es lo más sabroso Mira esta Mira
this now the
esta ahora tienen que estar diciendo los
others must be saying that's why that's why it's like a Battle
otros por eso por eso es como un Battle
royale
royale
playing among the corpses
jugando entre los cadáveres
Well that's how it is the first interaction of
Pues así es primera interacción de
meerkats with a
suricatas con
goat Why And that goat is new that
cabra Por qué Y esa cabra es nueva esa
goat is new Lili I just spoke to you
cabra es nueva Lili te acabo de hablar
on WhatsApp that tells you 24 hours 24
por WhatsApp que te lo dice 24 horas 24
hours eh Lili for the moment she has spoken
horas eh Lili ya de momento ha hablado
because she has posted a tweet not speaking is not
porque ha puesto un tweet no hablar es
speaking whatever she says whatever she
no hablar diga lo que diga diga lo que
says no no no she is a stalker she is
diga que no que no que es una acosadora
not going to stop she is a stalker only
no va a parar es una acosadora solo lo
the law is going to stop her only
va a parar la ley a ella solo le va a
the law is going to stop her what V you or I I am going to continue
parar la ley que V tú o yo voy a seguir
my my my wars my comings and goings
mi mi mis guerras mis idas mis venidas
what you have to do not see me Peppa
lo que tienes que hacer no verme Peppa
not knowing about me not knowing what I do what I
no saber de mí no saber qué hago que qué
am doing not knowing of course is what
estoy haciendo no saber claro es lo que
you have to do Forget me already
tienes que hacer Olvídame ya de una [__]
once and for all you went on a live show the other
vez que te fuiste a un directo el otro
day to say that I was your  idol that I
día a decir que yo era tu ídolo que yo
was her idol went to say Ah well it never
era su ídolo se fue a decir Ah pues no
fails eh this morning Lili has posted a
falla eh esta mañana Lili ha puesto un
tweet about the audience she's having
tweet de la audiencia que está
Look 200
teniendo Mira 200
200 she's had today in 24 hours
200 ha tenido hoy en 24 horas que
announcing that she's not going to talk about Javi the
anuncia que no va a hablar de Javi las
first 24 hours 200 has been her peak and she
primeras 24 horas 200 ha sido su pico y
's already crazy because he's going to come back because she does
ya está loca porque va a volver porque
n't know anything else she's not going to talk to you about
no sabe otra cosa ella no te va a hablar
herself she's not going to talk to you about other
de ella no te va a hablar de de otro
gossip and other gossip and no no no no no no no no
salseo y de otro chisme y no no no no no
that live was in the
no no no ese directo ha sido por la
afternoon and in the
tarde y por la
morning This look I do
mañana Este mira
n't know if you see it with the chat but 113
no sé si lo veis con el chat pero 113
users having been live for 63 minutes
usuarios llevando 63 minutos en directo
and he's not going to stop harassing because he doesn't know how to
y no va a parar de acosar porque no sabe
work he doesn't know how to do anything else he's not going to
trabajar no sabe hacer otra cosa no va a
[ __ ] and he's going to talk about any other
[__] y va a hablar de de cualquier otro
gossip about anyone who no no Javi
salseo de cualquier que no que no Javi
why do you have to be informing yourself about
por qué tienes que estar informándote de
what Javi does why do you have to
lo que hace Javi por qué tienes que
be watching Javi's live I mean you don't
estar viendo un directo de Javi O sea no
have to know what Javi has done You don't
tienes que saber lo que ha hecho Javi No
have to comment on Javi Because he
tienes que comentar nada de Javi Porque
doesn't have to exist no  you have to see it
no tiene que existir no tienes que verlo
you don't have to such but no no no no
no tienes que tal pero que no que no no
no she's a stalker who has an
no que es una acosadora que tiene una
obsession that she's a
obsesión que es una
stalker Okay
acosadora Bueno
guys look Juan got into the pool
chicos mir se metido Juan en la piscina
this one the video is going to be released on the
esta que se va a estrenar el vídeo el
main channel Let's see this let's
canal principal A ver vamos a ver esto a
see what happened and Juan and I
ver qué es lo que ha pasado y Juan y yo
know that you're waiting for the attacks that they've
sé que estáis esperando los ataques que
received and Juan and Plex You're going to see it
han recibido y Juan y plex lo Vais a ver
on Plex's Channel and Jo Juan's okay
en el Canal de plex y de Jo Juan vale
but I'm telling you see the profile picture that I
pero os digo veis la foto de perfil que
put the thumbnail
he puesto el la miniatura
no Juan has a [ __ ] up hand Plex and Juan
no Juan tiene la mano jodida plex y Juan
have been attacked by other animals and
han sido atacados por otros animales y
right now they're in the hospital
ahora mismo están en el hospital
getting injections because they're
poniéndose unas inyecciones porque están
[ __ ] I swear it's true okay I
jodidos os juro que es verdad vale os
swear it's true they're in the hospital
juro que es verdad están en el hospital
because they're
porque están
[ __ ] you'll see it
jodidos lo veréis
don't let me ra
no me dejas ra Por
Why don't you let me right
qué no me dejas la right Por
Why ah they haven't
qué ah que no la han
released it the mother who
estrenado la madre que lo
gave birth to it has released it
parió lo ha publicado
[Music]
[Música]
without without release The public
sin sin estreno La public
release
estreno
[ __ ]
[__]
well let the gossip continue they say out there let's
bueno que siga el salseo dicen por ahí a
see
ver
okay well we can  premiere the news
bueno bueno podemos estrenar el noti
Oh sure we can premiere the news and we
Oh claro podemos estrenar el noti y
do the rayal
hacemos la rayal
news okay come on put it on premiere
noti vale venga ponlo en estreno
schedule it for in 2 minutes and
prográmalo para dentro de 2 minutos y
put it on and that's it and Andy puts the
ponlo y y ya está y que Andy le ponga la
thumbnail and we do the Ray over there and
miniatura y hacemos la Ray para allá y
we go over there
nos vamos para allá
ah aiden made a mistake and he
ah se ha equivocado aiden y la ha
published it without a premiere but delete it and
publicado sin estreno pero bórralo y
extra it and that's it
estralo y ya
eh I don't
eh No
know I don't know you're going over there man and that's it you're
sé no sé os vais para allá mano y ya
not going over there man the
no os vais para allá mano ya está el
video of the success of the caa of gemita
vídeo del éxito de la caa de de gemita
sof is already published I already reacted
sof está ya publicado ya reaccioné está
the extract is here it is we leave it
el extracto Aquí ya está ya lo dejamos
there now I put it on Twitter and you
ahí ahora lo pongo en Twitter y usted os
go over there I'll see if andi puts the
vaya a mano voy a ver si andi me pone el
news on premiere and we go over there it's done
noti en estreno y nos vamos para allá ya
and I put the video in the pinned comment
está y le pongo en el comentario fijado
and in the pinned comment of the
vídeo y en el comentario fijado del
video I put the news it's done or in other words the
vídeo pongo el noti ya está o sea el
pinned comment the news I put the video
comentario fijado el noti pongo el vídeo
so that people go and come in it's done let's see
para que la gente vaya y entre ya está a
to me it seems like
ver a mí es que me da la impresión como
the premiere gives a good start to the
el estreno le da un buen arranque a los
videos But it's okay, whoever
vídeos Pero bueno no pasa nada quien
wants to
quiera
see it, Javi's live shows aren't long anymore.
verlo ya duran poco los directos de Javi
The truth is, I've been live
Pues la verdad es que llevo un directo
since 10:30 at night. I started
desde las 10:30 de la noche he empezado
on telesalseo for 2 hours and here we've done
en telesalseo 2 horas y aquí hemos hecho
the nonsense for one and a half. It's because
con la tontería una y media pasa que
I'm used to three or four
estoy acostumbrado a tres o 4
hours, but you have a newscast now and
horas pero tenéis un noticiero ahora y
a video on the main channel. I just don't
un vídeo en el canal principal es que no
understand the crying, man. I mean, people
entiendo el llanto tío O sea la gente me
want me as a total slave here. eh, they
quiere aquí de esclavo total eh sea me
want me submissive, submissive telesalseo doesn't
quieren sumisa sumisa telesalseo no
count, [ __ ] telesalseo doesn't count, but it's just
cuenta [__] telesalseo no cuenta pero es
that, eh, eh, it is. I'm fully active
que eh eh es Estoy full activo en todas
everywhere all day long. There's a video
partes durante todo el día hay un vídeo
on the main channel. There's a newscast
en el canal principal hay un noticiero
that's about to premiere right now and they're
que se va a estrenar ahora mismo y se
complaining that I've been live for a [ __ ] hour and a
quejan de que he estado una [__] hora y
half.
media en directo
Mondongo, okay, the news is premiering now, let's
mondongo vale está estrenando ya el noti
do the radio. Come on. It's
hacemos la raí
okay, we're going over there. Okay, we're
venga No pasa nada nos vamos para allá
going to the news. Westcol
Vale Nos vamos para el noti westcol
explodes against the King Lich. A
estalla contra la King lich un beso
huge kiss. Thanks to all of you who have
enorme Gracias a todos los que habéis
given gifts. Members 171 members
regalado miembros 171 miembros esta
here tonight.  taken out of dick okay And thank you
noche aquí sacada de [__] vale Y
so much for all the Super
muchísimas gracias por todos los Super
chats and for all the likes I'll see you
chats y por todos los likes os veo por
there okay I'll see you there guys don't
allí vale os veo por allí chavales no
touch anything you'll end up on the
toquéis nada que Vais a caer en el
news okay come on guys and those of you who
noticiero vale venga guapos y los que
are on Twitter we're on the channel
estéis desde Twitter estamos en el canal
we're at the salsería Okay come on
estamos en la salsería Vale veniros
[Music]
[Música]